I think that we need strong alpha males
like Donald J. Trump, Spencer Pratt, and
our loved Charlie Kirk
>> Did you just ironically say strong alpha
males?
>> We have laws in favor of women getting
leadership roles. We're taking
opportunities away from men. You are
oppressed more than me.
>> Men are men, and men have testosterone,
and men love beautiful women, and trust
me, I would prefer a man that actually
looks at women and is sexually attracted
to women.
>> Dude.
>> They had to make things up to get Trump.
Trump doesn't have to be a sexual
predator. Any woman would love to be
with Trump.
>> All right, listen. Put your hand up if
you would have sex with Donald Trump.
>> Has Donald Trump been a good president
for women, or has America moved backward
from expanding women's rights to
debating how far those rights should go?
I'm John Regalado and from Jubilee
Media, this is Surrounded, where one
brave soul faces [music] a room full of
disagree-ers. Today, we are diving into
what feminism means on both [music]
sides of the aisle, abortion rights, and
President Trump's record. I'm here with
our [music] featured guest, progressive
commentator Dean Withers.
Welcome to the show.
>> Thank you for having me.
>> You ready to go?
>> Oh, I'm excited. This will be fun.
>> All right, are you all ready to debate
Dean?
>> Yeah!
>> [cheering]
[applause]
>> All right, let's get it to it.
>> I'm Dean Withers. I'm a 21-year-old
liberal. I do political debate for a
living, and today, I'm surrounded by 20
Trump supporters again. But this time,
they're all women.
My first Surrounded claim is, men aren't
better at leading than women.
>> If you would like to debate this claim,
please get to the chair in 3 2 1.
>> Good to see you again.
>> Welcome back, Lori. How you doing?
>> I'm doing good. How are you?
>> I'm doing phenomenal. So, the first
claim is that men are not better at
leading than women. And I'm honestly
appalled that you as a woman would
disagree. But I mean, if you want to
start it off by telling us why you do
think men are better at leading than
women, the mic is all yours.
>> Well, how I would like to start this off
is I'd like you to define what a woman
is.
>> Well, sure. I think that the definition
of what a woman is is ultimately
irrelevant to this debate and I'm
willing to assume I'm willing to
pre-assume your definition of what a
woman is, i.e. an adult human female.
See, if I were to give you my definition
of what a woman is, an adult human
individual that pertains to the social
and cultural characteristic typical that
of a female sex index to their gender
identity, well, then all of a sudden
we're going to be speaking past one
another because we define the word woman
differently.
>> Exactly. So, you're bringing this
problem up in the first place is kind of
silly because you don't know what a
woman is.
>> Well, I just told you what my definition
of the word woman is. You just happen to
overlook that.
>> also depend on what leadership role that
that person would take. For instance, if
you wanted Kamala Harris, who you voted
for,
to be the president of the United
States, we have a problem with that and
I'll tell you why. It's not necessarily
the woman, but it is necessarily foreign
countries, for instance, the Middle
East. If I go to a Middle East country
as a woman, I can't show my hair at risk
of being stoned.
>> we talking about Middle Eastern
countries when the prompt is men are not
better at leading than men?
>> about leading. You voted for Kamala
Harris. I think she would been a
horrible leader. Foreign countries don't
always see women as respectful as they
see a man. A woman leading this country,
for instance, when you go to a doing
foreign policy and all of those things,
they would not have the respect that a
man would. I can also say as a woman,
depending on your age, if I've got PMS,
honey, I'm going to make different
decisions than I would as if I didn't.
If I'm going through menopause, I might
have hot flashes or whatever ever else.
I believe as a Christian woman, men are
supposed to lead. We're supposed to
help. And I'm totally comfortable with
that.
>> Okay, well, thank you, Lori. So, the
first thing that I'll to point out here
is that your position that maybe foreign
countries wouldn't respect a female
president as much as a male president, I
don't think is represented through the
fact that on the global stage Harris had
a significantly higher approval rating
than Trump during the election. And
there's a reason for that.
>> Cuz she would have been a pushover. They
would have got They would have walked
right over her.
>> And that's exactly why she had
significantly better policy, better
character, and would have been a better
president for America. But ultimately,
once again, Lori,
>> the topic of debate is not was Harris a
better option for the president than
Trump because even if we want to look at
women and men on this macroscopic level
of evaluating one woman compared to one
man, even if it was true Harris was a
clown and Trump was awesome, that still
wouldn't mean that generally speaking
men are better at leading than women.
The last point that you made there was
about PMS, and I think that you're like
indicating that women are more emotional
than men on average.
>> They are. 100%.
>> me why men commit 92% of violent crimes.
Tell me why they're more likely to
self-harm and allowed to commit suicide.
So, you think that testosterone is what
makes men more emotional?
>> Absolutely.
>> Okay, well then you just conceded the
debate.
>> No, I didn't concede the debate.
>> that absolutely men are more emotional
than men 5 seconds after saying that
women were more emotional than men.
>> and that's kind of like a somewhat of a
red herring because what I'm trying to
say to you, women are more emotional.
They just are in more of a
I can change my mind depending on my
mood. Now, you're bringing in anger,
you're bringing in violence, you're
bringing in
>> Is anger an emotion?
>> It is, but to a different extent. And
honestly, if you've got a man that's
violent, out of character alone, I don't
want him leading the country.
>> And that's why you voted for
>> Oh, yeah. You want to get into that? I
know that's another problem, but I'm
happy to get into that.
>> we can get into that as well.
>> accused. Never accused of
>> Okay, we got to we got to pause there.
You've been voted out. Please return to
your seat.
>> Good to see you.
>> Good to see you, Lori. If you would like
to be the next debater, please get to
the chair in 3 2 1.
Welcome. Welcome.
>> Hi.
>> I'm going to give the mic to you. Why
don't you tell us all why men are better
at leading than women?
>> Men are better at leading because as a
woman, I can tell you that we're
emotionally
uh manipulated very easy. We're tend to
be compassionate cuz we as a woman and
getting pregnant, it's in inherited in
us. Why? Because we deal with babies.
>> So, women deal with babies, therefore
women can be manipulated. I don't think
that that argument follows.
>> We're we're we're going to be easily
manipulated.
>> Women can be easily manipulated.
>> yeah.
>> What's the argument for that?
>> It's inherited in us.
>> Okay, just saying that it's inherent is
like me saying that what is actually
inherent of women is that they can't be
easily manipulated. That doesn't give me
any substance to underpin your position
when you just simply underpin your
position by saying, "Well, it's
inherent." And it doesn't push this
dialogue forward. I would say that men
are probably easier to emotionally
manipulate than women, or else they
wouldn't be culpable for 92% of violent
crimes. We could emotionally manipulate
a man by making him lose a game of
Fortnite. The next thing we know,
there's three holes in his walls. All
right, same thing with self-unaliving
statistics, suicide. Suicide's a really
bad thing, but it is true that men are
significantly more likely to kill
themselves than women on average. Same
thing with drunk driving, gambling. And
then when we look at women, they
actually perform better in the fields
that are less indicative of emotional
outbursts, such as performing well in
school. And I mean, this is all
underpinned by by biology. There was a
study done by the American Medical
Association that proved that if you're
operated on by a female compared to a
male in the operating room at a
hospital, that you're less likely to die
or to experience any post-negative
operative outcomes. Why? Because women
are biologically designed to deal with
stress and pain better than men because
they have thicker dendrites in their
brain. So, ultimately, the science and
the empirical facts completely reject
the conclusions that you formed.
>> Not at all. Men are more rational and
women
>> All right, you've been voted out by the
majority, so please return to your seat.
If you want to be the next debater,
please get to the chair in 3, 2, 1.
Hi.
>> Hi.
>> What's your name?
>> Annette Davis-Jackson.
>> It's a pleasure to meet you.
>> Yes, yes.
>> So, uh let's hear it. Why do you think
that men are better at leading than
women?
>> How about I know that men lead better
than women because women have the
babies, you're emotional, but more
important, I got I have a dad. I have a
dad who was very strong and when I see
what President Trump is uh embodying, I
say and I know that you can roll your
eyes, but you know what? My grandmother
used to say, "You can roll your uh
cotton balls, but you sure can't shoot
them." So, men are strong just like
Trump because in the first day first 100
days, what did he do? He started writing
uh executive orders.
>> Yeah.
>> He started writing executive orders day
after day after day after day after day
after day. Women would probably say,
"Hey, let me take a break." That's why.
>> Jesus Christ. Okay. Well, uh listen,
clearly I disagree with you about Trump.
Uh but, that's actually not relevant to
my counterargument. I'll tell you why.
Because even if Trump was a good leader,
that doesn't mean that therefore men are
better at leading than women on average.
Like for instance, in the same way that
you could give an anecdote of a man that
you think is good at leading to justify
the claim that men are better at leading
than women, well, I could just give an
anecdote of the opposite. Hitler was a
man, he was a terrible leader, therefore
men are worse at leading than women. All
right? But, clearly that's not how it
works because we cannot attempt to uh
allow an anecdote of what we think about
one individual man to then exist as a
portrait for a generalization about all
men.
>> Why did you have to say Hitler?
>> Because he's obviously a bad leader
that's a man.
>> Yeah, and and
>> The President of the United States,
which is the commander-in-chief, Donald
J. Trump, is a great leader.
>> Okay.
>> And he's a great leader because because
he won a landslide.
>> Okay.
>> And if he could run again, he would run
a landslide again.
>> Yeah, yeah. Well, guess what? He's not,
he's a terrible president, his policies
suck. How about this? What's your
favorite Trump policy? I mean a bill
passed through Congress then signed into
law.
>> I'm a former college coach and not
having men and women sports.
>> what bill was that?
>> Oh, no.
>> Well, I'm sorry, what bill was that? I
asked you a very specific question.
>> to stop there. You've been voted out by
the majority. Please return to your
seat.
>> Okay.
>> All right. If you want to debate this
claim, please get to the center in 3 2
1.
Hi Tracy.
>> How are you?
>> I think I remember you. Were you on my
first Surrounded episode?
>> Maybe.
>> Well, I'm going to pass the mic to you.
Tell us why you think men are better at
leading than women. It's uh it's worth
me like reminding you and maybe
everybody else in the room that so far a
lot of people who've come up and sat in
that chair have really missed the mark.
Like that last lady. She told me that
men are better at leading than women
because she likes Trump. Okay, let's
hear in general why men are better at
leading than women.
>> Well, this is why you're I think you're
going to be surprised. I actually agree
with you.
>> Then why are you in the chair?
>> And I dis- I respectfully disagree with
some of them. Well, I'm just saying some
of the points that they were bringing up
about a woman being pregnant and because
somebody's can carry a baby that they're
not fit to lead. I mean, it's the same
argument where we say
men go to work and come home and the
woman stays and handles the household
and the children. So, is that not a
powerful position?
And I also have to I'm I'm respectfully
disagreeing here and I want you to give
me an example if you can tell me
hypothetically of a woman that you think
would be a better leader than Trump
right now.
>> So so just to clarify, you don't think
men are better at leading than women.
>> No, no, D. Because if I'm in if I'm
>> happy I'm really happy that you don't
think
>> I I I told you I agree with you, right?
>> want you and everybody else in the room
to obviously not think that men are
better at leading than women, but
unfortunately, the nature of this
Surrounded episode is where we have
disagree-ers in the hot seat.
>> Yes, so I'm asking you.
>> you're not though.
>> So, if we're going if we're walking down
a dark alley, let's say we're on
Figueroa or something, I would be the
person having to protect you. I mean,
everybody's built differently. I feel
like I would have to be protecting you.
I'm taller. I I'm
I'm sure I weigh more than you. Uh I
mean you can take as many classes as you
want.
>> Wow. Yeah.
>> But it's true, Dean.
>> I'm not Listen.
>> Men and women are
>> I'm not going to disrespect your ego the
same way you're attempting to insult me,
and that's fine.
>> No, it's just it's a size comparison.
So, it it it depends on where this
conversation is going. If you if you're
looking at body
type that I'm sorry, there are women
that are larger than men.
>> vote her out because she doesn't think
that men are better at leading than
women?
>> Tracy, it does sound like you agree on
this prompt. So, we're going to have you
return to your seat and and bring in a
dis-agreer.
>> Okay.
>> All right, if you disagree with this
claim and you want to be the next
debater, please get to the chair in 3 2
1.
>> Hi.
>> Hello.
>> Your name's Julia?
>> Julia Kate. So, I want to ask you
inherent in your statement that men are
not better leaders than women.
>> Yeah.
>> There's the sense that you believe men
and women are different, correct?
>> I think that there's obviously
distinctions between men and women or
else we wouldn't have two different
words to refer to
>> Okay.
So, what are some of the distinctions?
>> Well, I mean there's distinctions in the
sense of cultural and social attitudes
and behaviors. There's going to be that
are of course innate to men and women
because I don't think that prescriptive
I don't think that prescriptive gender
norms exist. Now, like from your
perspective that we were to define the
genders on the basis of sex, of course
then there's going to be sexual
dimorphism and there's going to be
differences present within that. Of
course, like there's a plethora of
differences. Listen, I'm not denying
that there are differences between men
and women because once again if there
wasn't differences between men and
women, well then we wouldn't have two
distinct groups.
>> we agree on that.
>> My claim is is I don't think that any of
the differences that exist between men
and women would amount to being relevant
to justify the claim that men are better
at leading than women. And I'll actually
ask you
>> than at leading than men?
>> No, I actually think that gender's
completely irrelevant
>> Interchangeable is what you're saying.
>> of if somebody is better at leading than
the other person. I ultimately think
that there's going to be no
determinative ability regardless of
we're making the claim that men are
better at leading than women or women
are better at leading than men to ever a
that prescriptive claim.
>> hearing is that
>> and women are essentially
interchangeable in your mind.
>> Well, in my mind once again I just don't
believe in the proscriptive gender
norms. And I think that ultimately one's
gender is irrelevant to their leadership
capabilities. If you can tell me what
are the relevant differences between men
and women that make men better at
leading than women.
>> We can go back to the hunter and
gatherers when men were the ones going
out to hunt and women were the ones
staying with the children and gathering
fruits and nuts. Men are the people that
go towards risk, that go towards
provision naturally. Why is it that in
today's even our influencer community,
we have more women that are drawn
towards beauty, makeup, things like
family, schooling, and men are more
drawn towards traditionally masculine
things. It's innate in every culture
that you see this trend. We are
hormonally different. That's been
mentioned throughout this place. You as
a man do not know what it's like to have
a cycle, to have a period, to have your
hormones go up and down.
>> Yeah.
>> That is insanely significant for a
woman's ability to lead. And women will
complain about being scared to walk on
the streets at night and yet they'll
elect the same politicians that release
the criminals on the street.
>> that women should lose the right to
vote?
>> I think that we I'm not talking about
that today.
>> Can you just got to get a quick yes or
no then we'll go back to the topic.
>> need strong alpha males like Donald J.
Trump, Spencer Pratt, and our loved
Charlie Kirk.
>> Praise Jesus.
>> Have secure borders, who will not let
criminals on the street.
>> say strong alpha males?
>> Strong alpha males, yeah.
>> Bro, get a grip. Stand up. Listen.
>> grip. You're a man. Do you want to
mansplain to me?
>> Well, I mean actually you just said that
men are better at leading than women. So
you should listen every word that comes
out of my mouth per your perspective,
right? So if you think that men are the
strong alpha males and women are the
emotional followers, why don't you
follow my lead and listen to what I have
to say? Because you don't believe what
you say.
>> man. I believe that male and female are
created equal in the image of God. We
each have the same dignity and the same
value. We have the same brain, the same
rationality, but we have different and
distinct roles.
>> Okay.
>> Why is it that women can get pregnant?
Only females can get pregnant.
>> Well, of course that would boil down to
the physical biology that it
>> Physical biology suggests that
women are more geared towards child
rearing and child raising than men are.
>> So once again, the way that we started
this conversation was by me agreeing
that there going to be differences
between men and women. You just simply
disagree. Can I finish? I would love it
if I could finish. You can't say because
there's a differences between two things
that thereby innately one of the two
things is going to be better at leading
than the other. Like I think that's
ridiculous. Listen, once again, my claim
is that the differences that do exist
between men and women ultimately don't
amount to justifying the claim that men
are better at leading than women. Let me
respond because you made a lot of
claims.
>> You're going on and on.
>> I think it's been the opposite. To
respond to your claims, you said that
there's a difference in the hormonal
balances of men and women that what?
Make women more emotional? Well, I mean
I already went over this with a
>> It's not even just more emotional. It's
that our bodies are not equipped to
handle the same levels of cortisol as
men. We need more exercise.
>> Look at Donald Trump. The man literally
lives off of diet coke and McDonald's.
>> Okay.
>> We could not do that.
>> Okay. Okay. Listen. Actually, women are
more equipped than men to deal with
stress. It is proven by the science.
>> true.
>> No, I'll I'll tell you. You You can look
this up. Anybody at home can look this
up. Women have thicker dendrites in
their brain. And study after study after
study has concluded time and time and
time again that this gives women the
ability to better manage their stress
than men. And you actually brought this
up. You brought up childbirth. The
reason why women have thicker dendrites
in their brain giving them a greater
navigation ability, giving them a
greater giving them a greater ability to
deal with their pain and stress is
because of childbirth, okay?
>> Yes, because childbirth is what makes
women better leaders. We need strong
leaders. We need strong leaders. We need
strong leaders. We need strong leaders.
>> Plus once again, when we look in society
how men deal with stress compared to how
women deal with stress, well, when a man
gets mad, he commits a violent crime. He
kills his wife. He kidnaps his children.
He sets his house ablaze. And this is
why men are significantly more likely to
commit every single crime on the books
including crimes that do not have a
necessity for any use of physical
strength such as arson, cyberbullying,
>> If you think women are such good
leaders, why don't you let me speak?
>> Well, I'll happily let you speak in
response to the things that I've said as
long as you're able to stay on topic and
respond to me in the bottom of the box.
>> Because I'm a woman and I have a brain.
thank you very much.
>> Okay, well I guess women are better at
leading than men.
>> No, we're not. We're good at arts,
certain roles. We have our strengths and
our values. We're good at raising
children. We're very smart and
adaptable, but men are the people that
need to be out there fighting crime for
us, protecting us so that we feel safe
and we can keep our children safe. Why
do you think that just historically more
men are CEOs, more men are presidents,
senators, whatever kind of leadership
role you want to talk about? That is not
because of white supremacy,
colonization, or some kind of legal
limit.
>> Okay.
>> It's because men are drawn to those
roles. Today, women have the same exact
rights as men and still a lot of them
choose to stay at home or feel that they
can't stay at home because of societal
pressures.
>> Okay. Well, I think that you said it
there at the end, societal pressures.
Societal pressures are the reason why I
think that we've seen more men in
positions of power, more men in
leadership fields, and more men calling
the shot. But if you're the the position
that underpins your claim here would be
that if we see an overrepresentation of
men in a field in comparison to women,
that men are then by definition better
performing in that field. So in the same
way you're claiming that because of a
vast majority of leaders are men,
therefore women are worse at leading,
would you also claim that men are better
at surgery than women because 85% of
surgeons are men and 15% of surgeons are
women? I just want to direct yes or no
to my question so that I can follow this
up with a dialogue.
>> become surgeons because it's a more
masculine thing. It takes more masculine
traits. They have to look at the blood.
I said yes, but I want to ask you
>> I have to hop in here.
>> that men are more oppressed today than
women. Men are told that they're toxic
for being masculine. The only laws that
prevent any gender from getting a role
>> I need to respond.
>> We have laws in favor of women getting
leadership roles. We're taking
opportunities away from men. We
You are oppressed more than me.
>> This chick is crazy. Okay, listen. I
think that you're crazy because you just
said that I'm more oppressed than you
while also claiming that I'm a better
leader than you after making the
argument that disproportionately men
have been in positions of leadership
throughout history when leadership is
what grants power. But anyways,
insanity. Listen, I asked you a
question. I said, do you think that men
are better at surgery than women because
85% of surgeons are men and 15% of
surgeons are women. The reason why I
asked this question is because you made
the claim that men are better at leading
than women because a vast majority of
leaders have been men. You said yes,
Dean, because a vast majority of
surgeons are men, therefore men are
better. The science says no, men are
actually worse at surgery. So, the
American Medical Association did a study
in conjunction with the Journal of the
American Medical Association. They did
this study on 1.4 million patients over
six continents in 14 years, and what
they determined consistently is that
when we account for every single
confounding variable that could possibly
exist, every single time men are
significantly more likely to kill a
patient on the operating table or to
give them negative postoperative
outcomes in comparison to women. It is
one of the most well-accredited studies
ever conducted in human history that has
reasonably concluded that women are
better at surgery than men, even though
they account they account for minority
of surgeons. And this is exactly what
debunks your claim that if a field is
overrepresented by men, that therefore
men are better at performing in it.
>> and women are naturally drawn to.
>> But women are better at surgery, even
though they account for minority of
surgeons. That completely debunks your
argument.
>> Sure, that could be a thing, but I'm
saying that naturally men are drawn
towards roles of risk and provision.
That's because of innate biological
characteristics.
>> women are better at surgery.
>> said that you're oppressed because of
societal society telling you that you
need to be a beta, woke man. You are not
like oppressed as a leader. Like
instinctually, you want to lead. You
want to teach me. That's because of your
nature, and I appreciate that very much.
But I disagree with your claims.
>> Okay, well, I mean, you have to concede
here that your argument that men are
better at leading than women because
more men are leaders than women is is
false. And the
>> Okay, we got to
stop there. We're out of time. So,
please return to your seat.
>> Pleasure.
>> [applause]
>> That surrounded episode you watching got
you scratching your head again thinking,
damn, I've raid baited myself on a
Jubilee video again. Well, I got
something else that's going to do the
same thing to you or possibly teach you
something. You probably seen me before.
I'm Austin Hollyoake Broden, and I'm a
Christian populist.
>> And I'm David Maddix, and I guess I
could call myself a progressive. On this
show, we're doing something
revolutionary. We're trying to bridge
the gap in a uniquely divided America by
destroying these echo chambers and
addressing the issues plaguing everyday
Americans. Tune in to our show, The
Split, Sunday, June 28th on Jubilee.
>> My next surrender claim is Donald Trump
is a misogynistic sexual predator. Okay,
if you want to debate this claim, please
get to the chair in 3 2 1.
>> Hello, my name is Shiva Bagheri.
>> What's your name?
>> Shiva Bagheri.
>> Shiva Bagheri. Well, uh would you like
me to take it away by explaining to you
why I think Donald Trump is a
misogynistic sexual predator? First and
foremost, he's a sexual predator because
a court has held him civilly liable for
raping a woman by the name of Carroll.
Of course, raping somebody is something
that would make one a sexual predator.
In 2005, he also boasted about engaging
in sexual violence by sexually
exploiting beauty pageant contestants at
the beauty pageants that he owned by
barging into their dressing rooms and
looking at their naked bodies. And this
isn't an allegation from some woman that
you could defame and say just wants
money or fame. No, this was an
admittance of guilt, something that
Donald Trump said he did on Howard
Stern's radio show. And I see you
shaking your head. I'll happily play you
the clip if you want. And we also see
>> show me the clip because I do not
believe it. Yes, take it out.
>> Don't worry, I got it preloaded.
>> Okay, good.
>> So so you have done that. Now tell
>> Well, I'll tell you the funniest is that
I go backstage before a show and
everyone's getting dressed and ready and
everything else and you know, no men are
anywhere.
And I'm allowed to go in because I'm the
owner of the pageant and therefore I'm
inspecting it. You know, I'm inspecting
I want to make sure that everything is
okay. Everything is good.
Yeah, the dresses. Everyone okay? You
know, that's stated that with no
clothes. Is everybody okay? And you see
these incredible looking women.
And so I sort of get away with things
like that.
>> Why don't we start there? Mike's yours.
>> Okay, well, he said that he probably
sees them I it doesn't say they're naked
there, so I
>> It does.
>> They might have No, it doesn't.
>> He said that they have no clothes on.
When you have no clothes on, you're
naked.
>> No, who who said that they didn't have
clothes on?
>> Donald Trump.
>> He didn't say that in the clip.
>> Yeah, I'll show you.
>> Okay, again, I want to hear it again.
>> Everything is good.
Yeah, the dresses. Everyone okay? You
know, that's stated that with no
clothes. Is everybody okay? You know
>> There you go. Oh well, it's a club like
a he didn't actually say clothes, but
>> Yeah, yeah, I
>> He said club and
>> I I I think it's important for us to be
intelligent rational people. You say no
clothes. And then Howard Stern says, so
you're like a doctor.
>> don't agree with that. Okay, first of
all, I don't
I don't agree with that. Okay, I don't
agree with that. Um but men are men and
men have testosterone and men love
beautiful women and trust me, I would
prefer a man that actually looks at
women and is sexually attracted to women
>> Dude.
>> than someone that is not. And I actually
like looking at women, too, and I'm not
even a lesbian, but I think women's
bodies are beautiful. It's like
>> Ma'am, I'm sorry. No, no, I'm sorry.
>> This is disgusting. No, and
>> You just told me that you would prefer a
man who quote unquote likes the female
body and is willing to barge into the
private
>> that before. I said before that
I said before that
you're No, I said I don't
believe that's right.
You just lied about me right now because
I said I don't believe what he did was
right by going in there.
>> But I would prefer a man who likes to
look at the naked bodies of women that
got it.
>> been over someone that is attracted to
other men. Yes, absolutely. Because it's
not natural.
>> It's not natural to be gay.
>> to be attracted to the opposite sex.
>> Define natural.
>> Natural is what God made. Adam and Eve.
>> So God didn't make gay people?
>> Well, actually
No, no, that's sin and sin came from the
devil.
>> sin is a conscious decision. Being gay
is not a conscious decision.
>> Well, actually being gay is a conscious
decision. You It's an action. It's an
action.
>> choose to be gay?
>> Huh, yes, absolutely. I actually
couldn't choose to be gay when I was
younger.
>> choose to be attracted to your mom?
>> to a lot of women actually attracted to
me and I said no. And I said no. And I
said no.
>> If attractions are a choice, could you
choose to be attracted to your mom?
>> Huh, can you choose to be a pedophile?
>> No, I couldn't choose to be a pedophile.
Could you choose to be attracted to your
mom?
>> oh, so there you go. He thinks No, it's
an action, honey, and you can choose to
sin or you can choose not to sin. I I
try to keep the devil away from me.
>> get a clear answer to the question?
>> this is a clear answer. But see, you
don't come from a biblical standpoint.
>> What are the first four words of the New
Testament?
>> I I come from a biblical standpoint that
there's two sexes. There's no 50
different genders. That came from a
pedophile named John Money who lied
about a study to push reassignment
surgery on thousands of people through
his lie that butchered this poor boy and
put him through hell. Rimer twins, go
look it up on Oprah. Okay?
>> I'm going to ask the question again.
I'm going to ask the question again.
>> Jesus.
>> And a moral is a moral.
>> Okay, pause. Pause. Everybody pause.
Dean, we got to ask that you don't do
personal attacks. That's a warning.
>> Okay. All right. So, first and foremost,
the question once again was, could you
choose to be attracted to your mother?
The reason why I asked why I'm asking
you this question is because you had
suggested that all attractions are a
choice. So, please with a just a concise
yes or no, could you choose to literally
be sexually aroused by your mother? So,
there's two possible answers to this
question. The first possible answer is
yes, Dean, I could choose to be
attracted to my own mother. And the
second possible answer would be no,
Dean, I could not choose to be sexually
aroused by my own mother.
>> to do a hook on me. I
>> Could I just
>> Do you have a yes or no for that?
>> No, because this is a hook. Because I
will never be attracted to my mother, my
father, because I I it it it's a choice,
but I would never do that because I'm a
Christian.
That's
>> That's it. I'm not going to get say that
on camera. That's weird. And I'm not
going to be in the hook of this young
man that's 21-year-old telling a
52-year-old to put say something
disgusting like that.
>> Okay. So, you admit that it's disgusting
to think that you could choose to be
attracted to your mother.
>> We got to stop there. That you've been
voted out by the majority. Please return
to your seat. If you want to be the next
debater, please get to the chair in 3 2
1.
Howdy.
>> Hi Dean, how are you?
>> I'm doing phenomenal. I'm going to try
>> is Zuriel.
>> Zuriel, it's a pleasure to meet you.
We're going to go back to the prompts. I
think that Donald Trump is a
misogynistic sexual predator. The
reasons why I think this are some of
them that I shared with the last guest.
It's because I think that Donald Trump
is a at a civil court determined that he
raped a woman by the name of E. Jean
Carroll. Uh we listened to that clip of
Donald Trump bragging about engaging in
sexual violence. Listen, I take a sexual
predator to be somebody that is engaged
in sexual violence. Donald Trump bragged
about that when he said he'd barge into
the dressing rooms of the women at Miss
Teen USA and Miss USA. If Donald Trump's
admission of guilt in the clip that I
played to the last lady is true, and
this is indeed something that Donald
Trump has done, then by definition
Donald Trump would be a sexual predator,
and thereby by definition I'd be right.
>> Can we both agree that people in power
of elite, elitist people up there in
politics, all have their own maybe their
own immoral traits to how why they're
running for candidacy. Like we've heard
about Epstein files and there are all
these different people that, you know,
maybe they're not really here to make a
change for us.
>> Yes.
>> Can we agree with that? I could care
less about what Donald Trump says on the
media, cuz I believe as long as he does
his very best to be a good president and
do the best for this economy, I don't I
don't vote for a president based off oh,
their character. I don't I vote for them
based off what they can get done,
honestly.
>> I would like to just take a moment.
Let's look at what you said. Are you
saying Dean, it's true Donald Trump is a
misogynistic sexual predator, but I
could care less because of his policy.
>> What I'm saying is
>> Can I just get a straight answer?
>> can't deny that maybe he has bad traits
of his character. I'm not going to agree
that like I don't know everything about
Trump like you do.
>> Okay.
>> But what I care about is his economy. I
don't care about what he has to say
>> Let's let's start from the top of this
debate. You sit down. I tell you Donald
Trump is a sexual predator. I tell you
he's a sexual predator because he raped
a woman and boasted about sexually
exploiting beauty pageant contestants.
>> why I'm not responding to your question
is because I don't know
>> Okay, so let's just let's let's test
your logic. What do you say? Dean, even
if it was true Donald Trump was a sexual
predator because you don't know about
the evidence for it, which is something
you should look into on your own time. I
would still support him as president and
could care less. Is that your position?
>> still support him as president because
he's does what's best for the economy
and for the American dream.
>> Yeah. Okay, we got to stop. We got to
stop there.
>> You've been voted out. We got to pause
there. You wouldn't quote "I would still
support Donald Trump as president if he
was a sexual predator. If he was a
child predator I'd still support him."
>> If you want to be the next debater,
please get to the chair in 3 2
>> Hi.
>> I'm Liz.
>> Nice to meet you, Liz.
>> Nice to meet you.
>> Listen, I think that you've heard my
arguments. You happen to be sitting in a
position where you could hear my voice.
Mike is yours.
>> Okay, so my question is because you
mentioned Donald Trump going into the
women's locker rooms,
are all trans people sexual predators?
>> So I would not say that trans women are
sexual predators for using the women's
restroom. I think that the definition of
sexual violence would be any sexual act
that is done without consent and I don't
think that this would be true of trans
women who use a women's restroom. And I
have an argument for why I think that
trans women should be able to use a
women's restroom, but let's try to take
advantage of our time. Instead of me
giving you my argument, let's just
hopefully stay on topic with the claim
that Donald Trump is a sexual predator
because he's raped a woman. He has
boasted about sexually exploiting women
by barging into their dressing rooms and
looking at their naked bodies without
consent and telling Howard Stern how
much he loved how incredible they
looked. He's mentioned the Epstein files
over a million times.
>> the young women in sports who do not
want biological men in their dressing
rooms. Isn't that doesn't that go
against them?
>> Well, we can I can I can
>> I would love to have a conversation with
you about trans people in dressing rooms
or sorry, more so locker rooms. And I
understand where you're coming from if
you say, "Well, I don't want a trans
woman in my dressing room because I
would see their naked body and their
genitals." And the reason the reason why
I get it the reason why I understand
where you're coming from is because even
when I go into my gym's locker room and
I see other dudes with their dicks out,
I'm like, "Hey bro, I don't them to see
me. I don't want them to see see So, I I
actually I I advocate I advocate One
moment. I advocate for a uni a unisex
uni stall one person at one time
changing rooms in locker rooms in gyms
and sports across the country.
>> is, part of your part of your claim part
of your claim part of your claim is that
>> Well, you're not Do you accept that
Donald Trump is a sexual predator?
>> accuse you of being a sexual predator.
>> And if I admitted to doing it, then it
would be true. Donald Trump admitted to
barging into those dressing rooms, and a
court found him guilty of raping
Carroll.
>> No, he did No, they didn't, and that's a
lie.
>> They certainly did.
>> No, they didn't.
>> Yes, they did. Listen, do you accept uh
that the definition of rape would
include the penetration of a woman's
vagina with any part of a man's body,
including his fingers?
>> Without consent?
>> Yeah. So, specifically the action that
the jury found Donald Trump guilty for
was forcefully penetrating E. Jean
Carroll's
>> I think what's going on right now in the
world with men and women is that women
are accusing a lot of men of rape. And
until I see actual proof, because a jury
can just agree with anything. That's
That's something else, okay? Until there
is actual proof and evidence, and if you
can show me the proof that Donald Trump
her, then fine.
>> Thank you so much for the great
question. What's all the evidence? So,
the first form of evidence that we would
have would be E. Jean Carroll's
testimony, which has maintained
consistency for the last 30 years as
corroborated by four friends that
testified under penalty of perjury. The
second form of evidence that we have
>> lied under penalty of perjury.
>> Well, can you please like examine the
evidence in which I provide as soon as
I'm done providing it? We have therapist
notes from the '90s indicating she was
by Trump. We have the testimony of a
psychotherapist that said when E. Jean
Carroll was testifying to the fact she
was by Donald Trump, she was exhibiting
signs consistent with true trauma that
we'd expect to be onset by a true victim
of Then we have Donald Trump's lies and
inconsistencies. He lied. He said that
he never met her as a part of his
testimony for his defense. And then E.
Jean Carroll responded by submitting a
photo of them together to the court. We
also have I'm I'm I'm not done with the
evidence. I'm not done with the
evidence. We have another line
inconsistency on Donald Trump's behalf.
He also said that he never raped her
because she wasn't his type, but then he
confused a picture of E. Jean Carroll to
be his ex-wife Marla Maples under
deposition. So, clearly she was his
type. Then we also have E. Jean
Carroll's dress. E. Jean Carroll
submitted a dress to the court claiming
it was the dress that she was raped in
by Donald Trump. Court confirmed it had
male DNA on it, and then when the court
asked Donald Trump to provide a DNA
sample to test against the DNA in the
dress, he said, "No, no, no, no, no."
Doesn't sound like something an innocent
man would do. And then the last and
final piece of evidence we have would be
his character priors. Listen, we all
know that a one-time felon is around 73%
more likely to engage in another felony
compared to somebody that's never
committed a crime in their life. The
same thing rings true about being a
sexual predator. So, because Donald
Trump has character priors with engaging
in sexual predation, like the dressing
room clip, proudly boasting about
sexually exploiting naked women and
girls, or like the Access Hollywood tape
where he literally said that he would
just grab women by their vaginas without
asking first, and that's precisely what
the jury found him guilty of doing, or
everything to do with the Epstein files,
that in consideration with the direct
evidence submitted by E. Jean Carroll
and his lies, absolutely what
demonstrates Donald Trump raping E. Jean
Carroll.
>> Okay, we got to stop there. We got to
stop there. You The flags are up. You've
been voted out. Please return to your
seat.
If you want to be the next debater,
please get to the chair in 3 2 1.
>> Hi.
>> Nice to meet you. I'm Gina.
>> Nice to meet you, too, Gina.
>> Thank you. First of all, if Trump was
truly a predator, he would have never
reported Epstein to the feds.
>> Yeah, he didn't.
>> In the '90s. He did.
>> Do you mean 2006?
>> Yeah, sorry. 2006.
>> It's okay.
>> Also, was he ever on the island?
>> Well, I don't think that there's any
evidence to demonstrate he was on the
island. Cuz I don't think he needed to
go to the island to get it off. Listen,
about the 2006 uh quote unquote report
to the feds about Epstein, he didn't
report him to the feds. Epstein got
arrested, and then Donald Trump turned
around, called the local sheriff, and
said, "Oh, thank God you got him. We've
known about what Epstein's been doing
all along." Which A indicates that
Donald Trump knew what Epstein was doing
with Maxwell and didn't report him to
the cops prior to Epstein's original
arrest. And B indicates that Donald
Trump has been lying to us about the
nature of his relationship with Epstein
for the last 10 years.
>> No. all heard Donald Trump say that he
never knew what Epstein was doing, was
never involved, and was completely
oblivious. But according to that report
to the sheriff, of course he knew.
>> Okay, so first of all, if he did do
something, believe me, they would have
found it. They had to make the Russian
dossier up. They had to make things up
to get Trump. Trump doesn't have to be a
sexual predator. Any woman would love to
be with Trump. Okay, any woman.
>> a husband?
>> Um no.
>> Okay. Now wait, well let's actually test
that. Can I have all the women with
husbands or boyfriends in the room raise
their hands?
So her claim is that any woman would
love to be with Trump. Would you guys
cheat on your husbands and boyfriends
with Trump?
>> Well, that's a
>> Well, we didn't say if they were
married. Not if we were married.
>> any Instead of anybody who's in a
relationship, is there anybody who would
want to be with Trump?
>> do let's do the other way around. Okay.
>> predator. Who Okay. All right, listen.
Put your hand up if you would have sex
with Donald Trump.
>> If I was married to Donald Trump, yes.
And I'd love to be.
>> [laughter]
>> That's crazy.
>> Do you prefer Clinton? Why don't we talk
about sexual predators as far as Bill
Clinton?
>> Why? It's
>> Okay, because he's a because he's a
predator.
>> Okay, and if he is a predator, he's
going to be in jail. Okay.
>> Trump did report him to the feds.
>> I thought I clarified that's not what
happened.
>> I'm wrong. Show me that. Give me
evidence.
>> Virginia, first of all, Virginia Guthrie
worked at Mar-a-Lago in the early 2000s,
and he prompted her to come and work for
him as a massage therapist. Trump was
pissed, and he reported Epstein.
>> Okay, well I would recommend looking at
the fact check that will likely be on
the video screen that says, "Erm
actually, he placed this phone call
after Epstein was arrested to thank the
cop and to tip them off about Ghislaine
Maxwell." Cuz that's what the fact check
is going to say.
>> What's the difference?
>> Well, the difference is in one scenario,
he's reporting the crime to the cop to
then get Epstein arrested. In the
secondary scenario, he's thanking the
cop after Epstein's arrest, indicating
that he knew about what he was doing.
>> I think that in many scenarios what
we'll see from co-conspirators of
criminals is well once their friend gets
arrested for the same crime that they
committed will turn around and be all
lovey-dovey to the police to try to like
you know indicate and promote the idea
they were involved. And the only reason
why I bring this up isn't to say I know
with certainty that this is exactly what
Trump did but is rather to give
plausible doubt to your argument that
because he did this we know he's not a
sexual predator even though he admitted
to it on Howard Stern's radio show and
even though court found him guilty of
>> Eight, court never found him guilty of
First of all, if he was guilty of he'd
be in chains right now.
>> how civil courts work.
>> to make Yeah, it is.
>> Civil courts don't send people to jail.
They They hold people financially
liable. That's the nature of our
criminal justice system.
>> have been in jail.
>> You're not familiar with statute of
limitations then.
>> I'm familiar with that.
>> What's the statute of limitations?
>> You can only um accuse somebody within a
matter of time but right now it's 30
years.
>> if E. Jean Carroll, okay, came out after
the statute of limitations had passed
for sexual abuse in the state of New
York against Donald Trump, do you agree
that even if she had a video of it
happening to her, he wouldn't be in jail
because of the statute of limitations
had passed?
>> That's not true. There is no statute of
limitations when it comes to
>> So by the law, okay, the crime that
Donald Trump committed per the New York
state legal definition of and of sexual
abuse in 2019 through 2022 was was
specifically sexual abuse, okay? Because
legally speaking in New York, they only
define as penile penetration of the
vagina and she testified that he her
with his fingers instead of his penis.
So because of that it would be legally
categorized as sexual abuse and that's
the crime that had a statute of
limitations on it.
>> insane and they threw the case out just
recently.
>> Okay, we got to pause there. We got to
pause there. You've been voted out.
>> Um I just want to get a real quick raise
of hands. This is not to to shame
anybody. I'm just genuinely curious.
Raise your flag really clearly so we
could get a poll if at Donald Trump's
like, you know, when he was in his 40s,
if you think he was an attractive man. I
just want to get a raise of flags.
>> This is so concerning.
>> Keep your flag up if you think he is
currently still hot.
>> Currently is not.
Okay, I I I appreciate it. All right, if
you would like to be the next debater,
please get to the chair in 3 2 1.
>> All right, Lori. Uh Mike and the floor
are yours. What are your thoughts about
Trump barging into the dressing rooms of
the beauty pageant contestants?
>> you may not imagine this, but when I was
your age, I was a model.
And I can tell you for a fact every
fashion show, every modeling call, there
are men in the dressing room. There are
makeup artists, there are designers.
It's not uncommon. And you're making it
as if it's this big huge deal. Donald
Trump at the time was the head of the
Miss Universe and Miss USA pageant. It
wouldn't be surprising if I was in there
changing for him to walk in. And you
guys because it Oh, let's look at the
camera. He's got a face for that one,
too. Let's go to E. Jean Carroll since
she already went over this for 20
minutes.
>> to that?
>> Uh sure, but you we're down to 1 minute.
You've already talked about this.
>> Trump said that there were no men
anywhere.
>> Well, he I don't care what he said. I'm
saying as a woman that's been backstage
at many, many fashion shows,
>> She was the one backstage. She said that
>> Well, I'm sure that there were other men
forever or just that instance. I I'm not
buying it. Okay, we got 50 seconds. I'm
going E. Jean Carroll. E. Jean Carroll,
number one, the statute of limitations
had run out. Number two,
for a very long time, she never reported
it to anyone until Reid Hoffman paid her
to freaking go after this lawsuit, and
why she is now being charged with
perjury. Not only that, as a celebrity
walking into
uh Bergdorf Goodman's, you don't think
that anybody would have a picture of
him? And no offense, I don't trust a
woman that named her cat vagina and
freaking said was sexy and charged 21
other men with that crime.
>> Lori, you're going to get another
fact-check.
>> No, I Well, you go ahead and fact-check.
Larry King said rape was sexy.
>> you're wrong about Larry King, too.
>> Oh, no, I'm not.
>> a mess. Okay.
>> Your mind's a mess.
>> there's something quite barbaric about
MAGA, about this alt-right movement
that's hinged on this paraxis of
propaganda and useless and futile lies.
And then when anybody tries to check
these lies, well, then all of a sudden
the provocateurs of this movement get
mad, start screaming, start yelling,
start saying that they kicked our asses,
and then they don't let us speak.
Listen, you made a couple false claims.
You claimed that Carroll had said that
rape is sexy on an Anderson Cooper
interview. That's not what she said. If
you watch the interview with Anderson
Cooper, you will hear her say verbatim
that what happened to her was not
sexual, was not sexy, quote unquote, it
just hurt. And then Anderson Cooper
responded to E. Jean Carroll by saying,
"Well, I think that most people think of
it as like this hurtful, violent thing."
And then she responded by saying, "Well,
actually, I think most people think of
it as sexy." And the reason why she said
that is because we form our own versions
of reality predicated on our own
experiences. So, when you have the
experience of sexual violence, when you
have the experience of sexual violence,
>> It was a separate interview.
I've been through sexual violence. Have
you?
Have
>> When you go through the experience of
sexual violence, you're more likely to
be more hypercritical and aware of crazy
people in the world around us that
downplay it, legitimize it, or fantasize
about it. So, maybe it was descriptively
incorrect. It wasn't true when she said
most people think of it as sexy, but
regardless of that, that's not her
saying that she thinks of it as sexy.
So, stop misinterpreting the genuine
claims made by a victim of predicated
off of the trauma that they went
through. Quite frankly, Lori, I think
that is disgusting.
>> Well, I think it's disgusting because I
was a victim of actual and abuse. And if
you want to compare what happened in the
Epstein files, let me just tell you, I
was one of those little girls.
>> I'm sorry to hear
>> I was one of those little girls, but the
guy was Hugh Hefner. So, for you to sit
here and sit there and say it's
disgusting, I'm sorry, I don't agree
with the woman as a woman who was
abused. I don't agree with the attacks
falsely on Donald Trump because of the
crap that your side always has to push
because you got such bad TDS, it's
insane. That woman is a nut job. I knew
somebody that worked with her at Simon
Schuster said that she was so
inappropriate. She also accused 21 other
men of the same freaking crime.
>> Name five of them.
>> I don't know their names.
>> Because they don't exist. We're out of
time. We have to pause there. Great job,
everybody.
We are currently casting three new
episodes of Surrounded. If you're a
passionate debater who fits into any of
the categories currently on your screen,
we'd love to hear from you.
>> [music]
>> You can apply through our website
jubileemedia.com/casting
or click on the link in the description.
Feel free to spread the word to friends,
family, or relatives who would be eager
to join the circle. If you don't see
anything that you're right for,
>> [music]
>> fill out our open casting application in
our casting team will reach out if
you're a fit for future videos.
>> My next Surrounded claim is, abortion
should be legal.
>> If you want to debate this claim, please
get to the center in 3, 2, 1.
>> Hello again.
>> Welcome back. Mic's yours. I'll let you
take it away.
>> Okay, well, I have a question for you.
Do you believe in equality?
>> Well, I mean, I think that's a very
vague question, but generally, of
course.
>> Okay, so if you do, then all humans are
equal, correct?
>> Uh no, I don't think that all humans are
equal, and I don't think you do either.
>> Oh, I absolutely think that all humans
have a right to life, liberty, and the
pursuit of happiness.
>> Really?
>> It's part part of our Bill of Rights.
>> Okay.
>> And um if you actually love our
Constitution and our Bill of Rights,
>> then you would believe what I believe.
>> Well, I mean, it says people, but small
distinction there. I want to ask you a
question. Is it murder for a doctor to
pull the plug on a brain dead patient in
the hospital?
>> Um some people actually write what they
want done. You know, they say, "Hey, if
I become brain dead, then pull the
plug."
>> Yeah, but for instance, if they don't do
that, okay? Like for instance, I haven't
done that. If when I leave the set
today, I get into a nasty car accident,
I get T-boned by a drunk driver, I go
brain dead, okay? Would it be murder for
like my family to tell a doctor at the
hospital, "Well, because he's brain
dead, let's just go ahead and pull the
plug." Would that be murder?
>> I honestly, you're talking to someone
that is very skeptical of doctors, okay?
And even
they talk about brain dead people that
weren't actually brain dead. So, I you
know, that's why I I always leave up to
everything to God. So, when I die is
when I die.
>> to I want to clarify that.
>> actually don't want to be killed, but
now if you're you're on all these
machines to keep you alive, if it's
months and months and you're not getting
better,
>> Yeah.
>> um then you're using machines to keep
you alive.
>> But they're still alive and you still
don't think it's murder to kill them.
So, you actually don't think that all
humans have this intrinsic right to
life. And by the way, that's that's a
>> no. You don't speak for me. Again, I
just told you I don't believe in
doctors. So, I don't like I don't go to
the hospital.
>> very That's insane.
>> I I I I have not gone to the hospital in
a long time.
>> Okay, well, I hope that you you know, I
don't I want to add on a point of
clarification.
>> it's my time. Um now now question for
you.
>> All right.
>> So, when do you think life begins?
>> I think that life begins at the moment
of conception.
>> Good. I'm glad you believe that.
>> You're Christian and you base your
morality off of
>> science.
>> Christianity.
>> it seems like people that are saying,
"We're anti-science." They're
anti-science because they don't believe
man and woman, they believe genders.
>> to ask you a question about abortion.
>> Okay.
>> You made the claim that all humans are
equal. Every single human has the
identical right to life. That is a claim
that fundamentally everybody rejects in
one way
or
>> I didn't say that. So, see, you're
putting more into the sentence that I
did not add.
>> Your opening words were about equality
for everyone.
>> liberty and the pursuit of happiness.
Now, if you're a murderer, I do believe
in capital punishment, but because of
your actions.
>> Okay.
>> So, I That's where I don't believe in
equality is like Is a baby and a
murderer the same? No, because a baby's
innocent. A civil society protects the
most innocent and vulnerable. They don't
go and murder them. That is a satanic
society, and I reject it. satanic
society.
>> Okay, we got to stop there. You've been
voted out.
>> Okay.
>> If you want to be the next debater,
please get to the chair in 3, 2, 1.
Hi, Tish.
>> Hi, nice to meet you.
>> Nice to meet you as well. Why should
abortion be illegal?
>> Well, let me tell you ask you something.
Uh abortion is legal here. What What uh
procedure do you prep uh prefer? The
suction, the uh the dying uh Yeah. Uh
what what what what is it?
>> Uh I don't know. I'm the most gruesome
holistic gross one where we chop up all
their limbs and throw them in the trash.
>> Listen, really, that's gross. That is so
gross.
>> I know. I'm rage baiting you. Listen, my
>> four children
>> But
>> set of twins
I would never ever do that to my
children. Would you Would you have your
girlfriend do that to your child?
>> Well, ultimately, I think it's a choice.
>> a girlfriend?
>> I do.
>> Oh, you do?
>> Ultimately, I think that it's a choice
of the woman. So, if you want to tell me
that you never get an abortion,
>> No, I don't know.
>> power to you. I I I love that for you
because that's your choice, and I think
that's great. But listen, I don't think
that abortion is murder because I don't
think that there's any trait that we
could identify to be true of a fetus in
which we fundamentally would value
enough to grant the right to life. The
last person on the mic said, "Well,
fundamentally, all humans have the same
right to life." And that's something
that we hear from a lot of pro-lifers.
As I was attempting to communicate to
her, everybody rejects that view in one
way or another. So, I want to hear your
argument in so far as why it's morally
wrong for a woman to get an abortion
outside of it's gross
>> Because
>> Okay, grotesqueness doesn't arbitrate
morality. Like, taking a shit's pretty
gross. smells like right? But
we're not going to say it's morally
wrong to take a even though it's
gross. So, what's the argument that
abortion is wrong?
>> Let me just ask you this. Everyone's
really, really focused on, you know,
it's it's it should be the right to for
every woman. Why don't you think about
it the other way and think about why
don't you prevent all these women who
women who don't want to have babies, why
aren't you guys helping them prevent
pregnancies?
>> I I agree we should.
>> Yes, we should.
>> 100%. We need access to comprehensive
sex ed in schools. We need free and fair
access to contra to
to contra Yes, of course.
>> age?
>> Uh is at at an age-appropriate level. Uh
I would say starting in late middle
school because like I mean I I was in
middle school, you were in middle
school, we were all in middle school.
The second thing that I think is also
important here uh would be free and fair
access to contraceptives. And we should
also try to find ways to limit financial
instability in young women and young men
because the leading cause of women
accessing abortion is financial
instability. But you still haven't
answered the question and you've been up
here for a while. I want to hear why you
think that abortion is wrong. I think
that you're struggling to come up with
an argument.
>> it is murder.
>> And the definition of murder would be
the unjust termination of human life.
Explain why you think it's unjust.
>> First of all, a woman who has a
pregnancy, a baby in there, they have
they they have the right to life, too.
>> What grants the fetus the right to life?
>> What grants it the just that it's been
conceived.
>> fact that it's a human?
>> It is a human.
>> Okay, so brain dead patients have the
right to life, too?
>> So, what brain dead?
>> Yeah, they're human.
>> You know what? I've heard of brain dead
people humans coming out of comas.
>> Then they're not brain dead. The
definition of brain death is
irreversible cessation of all cognitive
function. Do humans who are biologically
alive because of machines with
irreversible cessation of all cognitive
function have the right to life?
>> I haven't really researched that. So, if
there was no hope, possibly.
>> Okay.
>> They shouldn't I mean that's not that's
and that's not my decision to make.
That's a family member's member.
>> Okay, okay. So, you think it should be
up to the choice of the family to kill a
human that doesn't have the right to
life. So, you don't think that all
humans have the right to life?
>> But if they're brain dead but if they're
brain dead but if they're brain dead,
are they really alive?
>> Yes, biologically they are.
>> You know what? That's a determination
that I I would have to take with a
medical doctor.
>> Let's say the same thing about women for
abortion, then.
>> No, I don't believe that
a woman has that even right that a woman
should be able to get an abortion here
in California.
>> Yeah.
>> No, I don't.
>> have to pause there. You've been voted
out.
Thanks for your time, Tish.
>> Okay, if you want to be the next
debater, please get to the center chair
in three, two, one.
>> Hi Dean, I'm Anya.
>> Nice to meet you.
>> Nice to meet you. So, I couldn't hear a
lot of what you were kind of saying a
while ago, but what were you saying was
brain dead people about if they should
be unplugged?
>> Well, I brought up a brain dead patient
as a counter example to the claim that
well, the reason why it's immoral, the
reason why it's murder to kill a fetus
is because the fetus is a member of the
human species.
>> Yes.
>> So, our brain dead patients on a
biological level
>> should not be unplugged. And I think
actually any argument that anyone makes
for a brain dead patient to be unplugged
is actually coming from the doctors who
want to harvest organs
and to promote the organ donation
industry culture. And I think that any
kind of promotion that even manipulates
families into unplugging their brain
dead relatives is also immoral.
>> Yeah, I think we agree. We agree on
that.
>> And so
>> So, organ harvesting aside, if a family
wants to unplug a brain dead family
member because it's the end of the world
>> That's immoral.
>> That would be murder?
>> Yeah. But I think the doctor it would be
murder from the doctor in the same way
that
>> So, you truly think it's murder to kill
any member of the human species. What
about a zygote?
>> That is also murder.
>> So, if I kill a unicellular organism,
I'm a murderer. Do you think that all
murderers should go to jail?
>> Human zygotes, it's about humans.
>> So, do you think that all murderers
should go to jail?
>> All murderers should be put into trial
and tried.
>> And if but if they're truly murderers,
like that's an uncontestable fact
>> Then yeah, they should be put to death.
>> They should be put to death?
>> I do believe in the death penalty.
>> Wow, okay. So, here's the thing.
Do you know what an IUD is?
>> Yeah.
>> So, an IUD, an intrauterine device, in
some circumstances will allow for
conception to occur, but then it will
implant
or then it will prevent the implantation
of the now conceived zygote.
>> of the IUD is to prevent
implantation. If it leads to death, then
it's not the then it didn't fulfill its
purpose. It went beyond that.
>> a secondary purpose. So, the main
purpose of an IUD would be to prevent
conception, but when that fails, the
secondary purpose is to then prevent its
implantation. So, if a woman knows that
sometimes IUDs will allow for conception
to occur, then they kill that conceived
zygote, and they still yet choose to be
sexually active, then inevitably they
conceive a zygote, and it dies because
>> Are you saying that when people have
their IUD implanted, it is not for
anything beyond just the prevention? Not
It is not done for the murder of any
kind of implanted
>> Well, because because it's a secondary
purpose and function of the IUD, if a
woman knows that, then she's agreeing to
the culpability of possibly having her
actions yield the death of another
person. Okay? And under your view, and
hopefully mine, that would be murder
given that the person that she's killing
through her actions by secondary order,
>> was not the primary purpose of the IUD.
>> Well, if I if I buy a gun with a primary
purpose of going hunting, but then one
day I get really mad, and I use it to
kill my neighbor, okay, I'm still a
murderer.
>> Um no, the primary purpose of the IUD is
to prevent pregnancy. Your primary Your
primary purpose is to hunt. Your Your
secondary purpose by that
>> example is a car.
If I buy a car to get from point A to
point B, but then one day I get drunk,
and I use it to like wipe out a family
of five, am I a murderer?
>> Yes.
>> Even though that wasn't the primary
function of the car?
>> Yes, because you used that car in the
same way that you used the weapon. You
used that car to kill someone.
>> So, even when it does kill a zygote,
under your view, it's murder.
>> But even though the primary purpose of
the car is for driving, you used it for
anything for something beyond that. It's
secondary secondary purpose was not to
be driven drunk and kill a
>> Well, the secondary purpose of an IUD is
to kill a zygote. But listen, I I think
that ultimately the primary or secondary
purpose argument is irrelevant, because
what we should be evaluating is did a
valuable life die, and is a person
culpable for the termination of that
valuable life? And if a valuable life
died, and a person is culpable for the
termination of that valuable life, and
it was not justified, then
>> because it was used
>> Okay, so I just want to clarify. You
don't think in all scenarios when an
individual terminates a valuable life
unjustifiably so and they are culpable
for said termination that they're a
murderer, well then you're just
completely redefining what murder even
is by introducing the abstract nuance of
this quote unquote primary or secondary
purpose argument.
>> the one who brought that up.
>> At the end of the day, the fact of the
matter is in many scenarios women will
get an IUD knowing that in many cases
the IUD will lead to the death of a
conceived zygote and they will know it
will lead to that in many scenarios.
Then they will still choose to be
sexually active and then the IUD will
kill. Under your view, that would mean
that that woman is culpable for murder.
Therefore, under your view that woman
should be executed.
>> You kind of said a lot of stuff. We're
going to pause there. You've been voted
out.
>> Okay.
>> If you would like to be the next
debater, please get to the chair in 3,
2, 1.
>> Howdy.
>> Hi, Shannon.
>> Shannon, Dean. Pleasure to meet you.
>> So, I want to know why you think that
killing babies should be legal.
>> Of course, because I'm a brutalistic
Satanist and I love the DNC and I'm the
leader of Antifa. Listen, the reason why
I think abortions should be legal is
because I don't think that abortion is
morally wrong. I think it's a
permissible action. And because I think
it's a permissible action, I therefore
don't see any good reason to infringe on
a woman's bodily autonomy in the legal
prevention of her access to abortion.
Therefore, it's a human rights
violation.
>> So, you don't understand that it's like
killing you don't think it's killing a
human being.
>> And you're okay with that.
>> Yes.
>> Okay.
Cuz I don't see any moral reason why
not.
>> more on preventable measures because you
can you don't have to have an abortion.
>> Oh, well I also disagree there. I do
think that we should focus on
preventable measures. In my optimal
society, there's zero abortions, okay?
Not because we're forcing women to not
get them, but rather because the
conditions in which lead women to get
them don't exist such as poverty,
financial instability, a lack of sexual
education, the failure of
contraceptives. In my ideal society,
those things won't exist.
>> Do you know that if a woman gets
pregnant she's not financially able to
keep the baby and she doesn't want the
baby, she could at least take Plan B.
>> Yeah. And I And I think that that would
be a good fact of sexual education to to
share with the world. That Plan B
exists. Well, I mean, actually, Plan B
is $55. There's off-brand versions that
are 20. And I think that that is a good
piece of recommendation. But ultimately,
if they don't take a Plan B or whatever
like happens after the pregnancy, they
should be able to access abortion. Hey,
I want to ask you this question. Do you
think that victims of should be able to
access abortion?
>> No, because they could also take a
morning-after pill if they get If I were
to get I would go take a morning-after
pill the very next day.
>> Wow. So, you think that a victim of
would have an obligation to maintain a
pregnancy. Is that because that if they
were to like satiate or stop the
pregnancy, the fetus would die? Okay, of
course it is. So, I want to ask you a
question. Do you know who Max Urby is?
>> No.
>> So, Max Urby is a 15-14 year-old guy and
he's in dire need of a stem cell
transplant. And this is a true story.
You can look it up. And his his stem
cell type is so incredibly rare that his
father set up a like a quote-unquote
fundraiser for his son, taking random
DNA samples and from people across the
globe. So far, they've collected 40
million samples and there hasn't been
one match. What this means is that
there's probably only one match alive on
the face of planet Earth that could
provide stem cells to Max Urby to save
his life. So, let's hypothetically
assume that you are the one and only
match for Max Urby's stem cell type and
the government finds this out. Then the
government forces you to provide your
stem cells to Max Urby without your
consent for 9 months, introducing many
physical and mental complications. Do
you think that'd be just?
>> No.
>> No, because they shouldn't be able to
force you to provide your bodily
resources to another life even if not
providing your bodily resources would
mean that other life dies. That's my
position on victims of They shouldn't be
forced to provide domicile in their
uterus and access to their bodily
resources to the fetus even if stopping
the sustenance of those bodily resources
to the fetus means the fetus dies. No
different than Max Urby.
>> This is a tough one for me cuz I I have
mixed feelings about it, obviously, cuz
that's a horrible situation to be in.
But I do, like I said earlier, morning
after pill.
>> Well, could you respond to the argument
again?
>> have to pause there. You've been voted
out. Hey, listen, I appreciate you for
the respectful dialogue.
>> By the way, I want to tell you I respect
you a lot. I saw you when you cried for
Charlie Kirk. You actually have a soul.
>> Have a good one.
If you want to be the next debater,
please get to the chair in 3 2 1.
>> Hello, I'm Georgia.
>> Georgia, pleasure to meet you. You said
that you work for a pro-life org?
>> Yes, I do.
>> Very, very interesting.
>> talk about it.
>> You guys focus on like preventative
means from pregnancy in the first place?
Like do you guys have like policy
initiatives to like reduce financial
instability or poverty in young women?
>> abortion does is it incentivizes people
to live in a promiscuous way that
further increases the rates of
um pregnancies that are not in a stable
situation like marriage. And so, I'm
actually against contraception.
>> Being pro-contraceptive would save the
lives of more innocent babies under your
view because there would maybe less
unwanted pregnancies.
>> being is always wrong. Abortion kills an
innocent human being. Therefore,
abortion is always wrong.
>> Yeah, I reject people who
>> And allowing abortion just reflects our
overall decay as a society when it comes
to the way we view sexuality, marriage,
and it just leads to a culture of death.
When you have abortion, it leads to
things like made in Canada. What
abortion is is we're allowing the
government to have the authority to
define when personhood begins because
we're separating it from the moment of
conception. And if it's not at the
moment of conception, then the most
powerful person gets to decide when it
begins, and that's always subjective.
And when more powerful people have that
authority or allow themselves out of
that authority to define when personhood
begins, you have grave travesties like
slavery. If it's a subjective line, then
when does that begin? When does
personhood begin? And when you say it
doesn't begin at conception, it's
actually what you're arguing is a very
suspicious mystical idea of when it does
and that sounds more superstitious than
Christianity.
>> Well, thank you for your comments. About
your syllogism, I'd reject P1. Don't
think it's always wrong to kill an
innocent human being.
>> kill an innocent human being, you don't
think it's always wrong to intentionally
kill an innocent human being.
>> I've said to the last five guests, I
mean, we do that to brain dead patients
all the time.
>> Okay, so that's to withhold care from
them. That's sustains their life. That's
different than intentionally going there
and killing them.
>> Okay, so then you're on board with the
abortion pill, withholding the
progesterone and supplied through the
umbilical cord that would sustain the
life of the fetus.
>> I I'm completely against the abortion
pill.
>> it's just withholding care that would
sustain the fetus's life.
>> it's different though in nature because
what we're doing is what happens occurs
in the uterus is solely for the service
of the fetus. The uterus does not exist
to serve the woman. They exist to serve
the child.
>> Mhm.
>> What abortion is is it's just the actual
destruction destruction of that child.
It reflects the destruction of our idea
of parental duty. Parents have a duty to
care for their children. What's your
question?
>> Uh my question is, let's just like
envision a hypothetical of like a
9-year-old girl getting impregnated
and we know that pregnancy is not going
to kill her. Per your syllogism that you
gave earlier, it seems to be the case
that you'd argue it would be wrong for
her to get an abortion. Is this true?
>> Abortion only continues to perpetuate
violence, the cycle of violence. It only
increases the trauma to that child and
what we would do we would still try to
minimize the the trauma of pregnancy for
that 9-year-old.
>> I am completely against abortion in all
cases, period. And that's the
>> That's the consistent pro-life stance.
>> Wow.
>> I
>> What about when it's like the life of
the mother on the line?
>> Okay, so that's nonsense. What we have
is exactly we have C-section. And so
>> What if it's before viability?
>> That simply does not happen. That simply
is a lie of the law.
>> There's no what ifs. Listen.
>> I know it's a it's a good question. But
by the way, it does absolutely
>> it does absolutely happen.
>> Okay, our medical technology is so
sophisticated today
>> Could you just answer the question like
would you be okay with it?
>> that there is a black and white the life
of the mother. The technology we have
today is where we can we can try we can
operate on fetuses and the child can
continue
>> If a medical health professional
determines that a pregnant woman will
die if she doesn't get an emergency
C-section or abortion.
>> do the emergency emergency C-section,
Dean. You just proved my point.
>> No, I didn't because it's
before viability.
>> Okay, when's viability? Viability is
based on technology, not viability
changes.
>> It It is. I mean I just want to ask my
question.
>> One day viability might be in the first
trimester.
>> The question that I'd like to ask you is
let's assume a woman is pregnant. It's
before viability uh per the techno-
technological innovations and standards
in America cuz that's where we live.
>> personhood begin, Dean?
>> I'll happily answer your question if you
like.
>> abortion be legal?
>> So, I think that personhood begins
around 20 through 24 weeks with the
thalamocortical connections in the fetal
mind, but my question is if there is a
woman that's pregnant, it's before
viability uh per like the technological
innovation in America, and a doctor
tells her that she needs to get an
emergency C-section or abortion. It
doesn't matter because either way it's
going to kill the fetus, and the doctor
says if she doesn't get this emergency
C-section or abortion, then she's going
to die. Would you be okay with her
getting what I just interested. It's a
It's It's I want to see where your
ideological underpinnings fall.
>> So, I notice how that's one of your
debate strategies. You corner us into
these questions. I'll answer your
question.
>> Thank you.
>> So, what doctors do is they take an oath
that says do no harm. Doing an abortion
not only does obvious harm to the child
by killing the child, but it actually
does a lot of physical trauma to the
mother. It does a lot of trauma to the
uterus. And not only that, but many
women end up being suicidal after
abortion. But regardless of that,
>> answer the question though?
>> very backwards view of the technology
that we have now. There simply are not
cases where women need to get abortions
>> Notice how she's not answering the
question.
>> because it's not a scenario that
actually exists. A lot of these doctors
are committing medical malpractice, and
they're actually lying because they have
an agenda.
>> They don't even If it were to happen,
would you be okay with that woman
getting an abortion?
>> Absolutely not, because that doesn't
happen.
>> So, if it did, you wouldn't be okay with
her getting an abortion? That's insane.
>> does, see we're talking about
>> going to pause there. We've got to pause
there. We're kind of at an impasse. Um
we've also run out of time, so we're
going to move on.
My next surrounded claim is, Donald
Trump is a terrible president.
>> All right. If you want to debate this
claim, get to the chair in 3 2 1.
>> Hi.
>> Hi, welcome back.
>> Yeah.
>> I don't know, let's see. Donald Trump is
a terrible president because he slept
his way to the top.
>> No, I actually think that
>> Remember that? It was brutal. Hey,
listen. Floor's yours. Why do you
support Trump?
>> I think that he has done a He's
obviously done a lot of things. I can't
say he's a perfect person, but I do
think he has done things to benefit us.
>> What is one macroeconomic indicator
that's better off today than it was a
year and a half ago under Biden?
>> Closing the borders.
>> So, that's not a macroeconomic
indicator. A macroeconomic indicator
would be something like GDP growth,
unemployment, inflation, jobs reports,
uh and by definition, a macroeconomic
indicator is just simply a gauge that we
could use to determine the health of the
economy overall. So, once again,
speaking about GDP growth, inflation,
like wages, so on and so forth.
>> if I can I can dive into that?
>> One indicator that's better off today
than it was a year and a half ago under
Biden.
>> Um the amount of drug use and fentanyl
in society has gone down miraculously
because he has closed the border, and
illegal drugs are no longer allowed to
come in.
>> Do you understand the question I'm
asking you?
>> Yeah, I do, and I'm answering it.
>> So, the amount of people that use drugs
in society could of course influence
macroeconomic variables. Like, if
everybody was drugged up all the time,
nobody could go to work, right? So,
therefore, the macroeconomic indicator
of like unemployment would be really
high. Okay? So, it's not directly the
macroeconomic indicator, but rather it's
an influence of the indicators. So,
directly, what is one macroeconomic
indicator that's better off today than
it was a year and a half ago? Keep it in
mind that macroeconomic indicators are
things like inflation, GDP growth, wage
growth, real median wages,
uh unemployment, job reports, so on and
so forth.
>> Same thing. I'm going to go with drug
use.
>> Stop it, dude.
>> Okay.
>> Dude.
>> Listen. So what macroeconomic indicators
does drug use influence? Are you saying
that now we have like a lower level of
unemployment because of that?
>> by closing the border and not allowing
illegal people in here giving me and so
many other people job opportunities that
they weren't allowed to have before
because companies were employing illegal
immigrants just like the weed farm in
California that Newsom was directly
supporting. They had children at the age
of 9 years old illegally here working
for them. Those people are no longer
allowed here giving the job
opportunities to others. That is
benefiting the economy.
>> Okay. So is that why we added the lowest
amount of jobs to the economy in 20
years ignoring recessions last year
under Trump? Is that why we have the
highest level of unemployment since the
pandemic?
Yeah, it's not. The reason why mass
deportation
The reason why mass deportation doesn't
open up job opportunity in America is
very simple. Because ultimately
undocumented immigrants as a demographic
are very economically productive. They
pay over a hundred billion dollars in
taxes per year at the federal, state,
and local level. And they pay in 1.1
through 1.7 trillion dollars to the GDP
annually. And according
So that's
So my source is the IRS. Do you think
the IRS is lying?
>> Absolutely. I'm sure I'm sure they can
lie about statistics all the time.
>> So Donald Trump's IRS is lying about how
much
>> Trump's IRS.
>> Well, that's what the IRS is saying
today. Who's the president?
>> No. Well, this is the The statistics
came in from years ago. You've used that
since the last time we were here.
>> Do you know who Scott Brison is?
>> No.
>> He's the administrator of the IRS. Do
you know who he was appointed by?
>> Donald Trump, I'm going to assume.
>> And Scott Brison and the IRS under Trump
still report that. And listen, it's it's
it's not a contestable fact.
>> population can't allow opportunities for
others to come in. You realize I have I
have I have
>> Because it makes the economy
>> family that are refused opportunities,
health care, and other resources due to
the fact that it's oversaturated by
people do who do not have a citizenship
here. And by closing those borders and
not allowing those people to come in, it
gives them the space to have that
because that's what my tax dollars
should be paying for.
>> that undocumented immigrants can access
like federal Medicaid, Medicare, or
something like
>> actually. They can't.
>> Do you Do you know what the Personal
Work Order and Responsibility Act is?
>> I I actually know that they can because
I have family members that perfectly
walk in and they can get checks month
per month, living month per month, and
we support that. Our tax dollars that we
pay, we support that.
>> a yes or no? Do you know what the
Personal Work Order and Responsibility
Act is?
>> I believe it has something to do with
jobs and paying taxes no matter your
>> No. The Personal Work Order and
Responsibility Act is a bill from the
'90s that strictly limits and prohibits
any type of federal public welfare
benefit from being given
to
>> the law, obviously. Here in California,
we
>> undocumented I'm going to continue to
speak. There was one slight addendum to
this with Obama's I'm Tall of which just
says that undocumented immigrants can
get life-saving emergency care if they
need it. But, the point is, when you
suggest that undocumented immigrants are
relying on these federal systems of
benefit
>> are.
>> anyway from Medicaid to Medicare to to
Section 8 to food stamps, they're not.
It is literally illegal for them to
collect those benefits.
>> And they do anyway because states like
California allow it. We pay for it. I
believe No, I'm not confused.
>> confused about is the difference between
limited state-level benefits and federal
benefits. So, you're right.
>> But, it still happens on some level. Can
you acknowledge that?
>> In 10 of our 50 states, undocumented
immigrants have the limited ability to
collect social safety net
>> still an ability and my tax dollars in
California are paying for it. Yes.
>> Well, actually their tax dollars pay for
it because they pay $100 billion per
year in taxes. That's what I told you.
>> And people people like my brother with
disability that truly need those things
are being cut
>> different systems.
>> Absolutely not.
>> Yeah, they are.
>> Nope.
>> What's Medi-Cal?
>> Medi-Cal? My brother gets Medi-Cal and
they also get Medi-Cal. Yes, they do.
>> of benefit for undocumented immigrants
that no longer exists.
>> My brother literally just got something
in the mail that says for Medi-Cal.
>> Your brother's on Medicaid on the state
level.
>> Medicaid.
>> Listen, I The point that I'm trying to
make here
>> I'm filing for a conservatorship for my
brother. I would know exactly what he
gets. And he's getting cut by day
because of the over saturation and the
over population of people we don't even
know exist and we're not paying for
them. So, do we not acknowledge that by
closing the borders like I'm going to go
back to my point just like you like to
do with everybody else? I'm going to go
back to my point that by cutting that
population off and allowing more space
for opportunity for Americans would
benefit the economy.
>> So, you're saying that you pay for the
benefits of undocumented immigrants when
they're paying over a hundred billion
dollars per year in taxes in the
federal, state, and local level. Uh
well, guess what? They're paying for
their own benefits in the ten limited
states that give them. In fact,
>> do their jobs.
>> this is this is just
anti-intellectualist propaganda. That's
what the IRS says. That's what the Cato
Institute which is run by libertarians
which is right leaning society.
>> Okay, well, let's pause there. Let's
pause there. You've been voted out.
>> Hater.
>> All right, if you want to be the next
debater, get to the chair in three, two,
one.
>> Hi, nice to meet you.
>> Hi, ma'am. It's nice to meet you.
>> you, too. I want to talk to you about my
point of view as a Mexican American
Jewish.
I'm not saying Trump is perfect, but I'm
saying this the reason I vote for him
and I would vote again. First of all, I
want to touch the point that she said
about borders but not about the people.
I'm talking about the drugs and the
traffic that is coming from my country
and it's from from my government because
Mexico has a narco government. You know
who's the only one who has the guts to
go right now and deal with the
president?
Trump because the other administration
didn't do it.
>> Yeah.
>> Who went to bring Venezuela Maduro to
the jail?
Trump. And this is affecting United
States.
>> Yeah.
>> I mean, I'm not saying everything he's
doing is great and I'm Jewish so I
support Israel. Who is the only one
who's supporting Israel? Trump.
Otherwise, I don't know how we're going
to be right now.
>> Oh, yeah. Let's let's support a state
that's committing
genocide and ethnic cleansing in
Australia.
And Lebanon. And let's make sure to
throw one billion dollars a day at a war
that's killed thirteen of our servicemen
and women for another state per the
testimony of Joe Kent. Listen, okay,
there's my point. I want to respond
I want to respond to the first claim.
>> is the first ally of United States. So,
we have the right to [clears throat]
support Israel. And you know what? God
said to Abraham, I will bless whoever
bless you and I will curse whoever
whoever curse you. If you want to be
blessed in this country need to be
blessed needs to bless Israel first.
>> Yeah.
You be the prophet.
>> has been every single country who has
been cursed Israel is Look how they are
right now. Do you know that?
>> It's not religious.
>> It's genuinely religious psychosis.
>> Do you see how Chavez ended? He cursed
Israel from the from
his death and he said it from his and
he's dead.
>> Yeah, we have to bless the ethnic the
ethnic expansionist genocidal
terroristic state or else we're all
going to be cursed and die. I want to
respond to the first couple claims that
you made specifically on topic with
Venezuela and the border. So, who brings
in 70 to 80% of the drugs into this
country per the homeland of
homeland of border security?
>> Mexico, Colombia, Venezuela. Who is
bringing them? Who is supporting them?
It's Mexican country and I'm sorry to
say it. I love my country, but my
government is
>> Okay.
>> disgusting
>> Thank you for your response. So, 70% of
the drugs sold in America brought into
America are brought in by citizens. Why
do I bring this up? Because when we say
the undocumented immigrants are the
issue, they're the people that are just
bringing all these drugs across the
border then they come here to like women
and kidnap children and commit all these
heinous violent crimes is nothing more
than demoni- is the demonization of a
demographic that's actually very
beneficial
>> Documented people are the one who
bringing
to become citizens.
>> And that's why you shouldn't support
Trump.
>> I'm not telling you he's doing
everything perfect. I never said that.
I'm talking about the borders that he we
have more than 2,000
miles border with Mexico and that's
where they come drugs and that's where
they come this trafficking
>> Listen, I don't
through legal ports of entry for the
most part.
>> They are killing our people in the
streets right now.
>> once Once a vast majority of the drugs
uh drugs brought across the border are
brought in by citizens through legal
ports of entry. And it it when when I
give you an explanation for this, it's
going to make sense to you because think
about it. Okay, when a citizen is coming
in through a legal port of entry, okay,
well, nobody just has the innate right
per the state to pull them over,
scrutinize them, check every uh you
know, nook and cranny of their vehicle
because of our Constitution. But when,
you know, they identify an undocumented
immigrant, well, they already have uh an
individual who's capable of breaking
federal law, so then they have all the
rights in the world to detain them and
arrest them if they need to pat them
down or check their vehicle. And that's
why a lot of the drugs that come into
this country will come in with citizens.
But I think my larger point here is I
don't think that Donald Trump has
secured the border. I think that the
reason why we've seen such a drastic
decline in undocumented entry has
nothing to do with proactive long-term
border policy, but rather to do with
fascism and human rights abuse. There
are people in this country that are
getting illegally deported and then
tortured in places like Secot. Executive
Order number 13160 attempted to
unconstitutionally reclassify citizens
as undocumented immigrants to be lined
up and deported by the DHS. We're we're
watching people like Alex Fredrickson
get murdered in broad daylight by ICE
agents.
>> to answer to you before you continue.
You're talking about legal
interpretation. I I used to be a foster
care liaison. When all these kids in
cages, that was not true. I was there.
They called us for an emergency meeting
looking for families to support these
kids meanwhile they were reunificated
with their families. Reuni-
reunification with their families. Yes,
it was not true they were in cages. That
was just the media what they wanted to
portray.
>> So, your argument that Executive Order
number 13160 doesn't even exist?
>> What I'm saying is the media wants to
say what they want to say because they
have already, you know,
>> But this isn't coming from the media.
It's coming from the White House
website.
>> All right. All right, if you want to be
the next debater, please get to the
chair in 3 2 1.
>> Hi, welcome in. Um I think we should
start this off a little bit.
>> even sit down.
>> I know, I'm talking to you while you're
standing up. Hi, I got Okay, I'll slow
it down. What's your name?
>> I'm Katia, but you can say Tia. It's a
lot easier.
>> Well, it's a pleasure to meet you, Tia.
Thank you for being here. Listen, I say
we start this conversation off a little
bit differently. Can I tell you why I
think Trump is a terrible president?
>> That's what I was going to ask you. I
would love to know, actually.
>> Perfect. Well, I break it down into the
three main categories. There's domestic
policy, his foreign policy, and his
character. Okay? He is the worst
president of my life, the worst
president of your life, and the worst
president of the lives of every single
person sitting in this circle. Let's
start by evaluating his character. He's
a 34-count felon, a adjudicated rapist
that has posted about perving on the
naked bodies of beauty pageant
contestants, depicted black people as
monkeys on his Truth Social, and was
sued in the '70s for refusing to rent to
black people because he thought that
they were  poor. And there's
about a billion other things I could say
because of the time on the clock, I'll
keep it concise. We look at his domestic
policy. There's not a single
macroeconomic variable that is better
off today under Trump than it was a year
and a half ago under Biden. GDP growth
is down. We got one of the worst jobs
report in modern American history last
year, adding only 170,000 jobs to the
economy after adding 2.2 million under
Biden in 2024. We see that unemployment
is up. We saw 1.3 million layoffs. We
see the highest increase in the price of
gas in 1 month since the Vietnam War in
1967. Foreign policy is a disaster. He
said he was going to end Russia's
invasion of Ukraine on day one, he
didn't. He said he was going to bring us
closer to our allies, now they all hate
us because we imposed unconstitutional
legal tariffs on them. He said he was
going to be the president of no new
wars, then he started a new war of
choice in Iran just to deflect away from
the Epstein files. And this holistic is
why I think that Donald Trump is a
terrible president. The mic and the
floor are yours.
>> Okay, thank you. Um so
I haven't been in politics that long as
far as like interest. It was like 2016
really opened my eyes. I never thought
Trump had a chance, honestly. But I do
seem to remember in 2016 a lot of the
dialogue around his win was he only won
because America's racist. Basically
saying everyone who voted for him was
racist. This is after eight years of
Obama, by the way, who got reelected.
So, based on that and after four years
of not being president and now he's
back, why do you think that he won if
he's one of the most terrible presidents
in our lifetime?
>> Okay. Yeah, I'll give a direct answer to
that question. I first want to ask you a
clarifying one. Do you think that Biden
was a bad president?
>> I don't want to talk about Biden cuz
that's not why we're here.
>> Right. Okay. Well, I'd expect you to
answer that question to be no, of
course, but Biden got the most votes out
of any president in history. We can't
say just because people were willing to
vote for a candidate to be president
that therefore they were the best
option. The reason why I think that
Trump won the election had a lot to do
with propaganda surrounding the negative
economic impacts of the pandemic, okay?
We saw 9% high levels of inflation,
roaring gas prices, and I don't think
that these things were caused by Biden,
but Biden never was really too publicly
outspoken about that. And I think that
was a messaging problem with the Dems.
The second reason why I think that
Donald Trump won had to do with the fact
that Kamala Harris only had a little bit
over 100 days to run, which I also blame
blame on Biden. He should have stepped
down a lot sooner. But ultimately, I
don't think Trump won because he's a
good president, and that's undeniable.
Has your life gotten better in the last
year and a half?
>> My life has gotten better, actually.
>> made it better? Tell me specifically.
>> I I honestly do feel safer with him
president. I mean, we can beat a dead
horse with the with the closed border.
That means a lot to me. Like, I'm a mom.
I have kids. It's important to me that
and I live in LA, which is like crazy,
right? Do you live out here or no?
>> No, I don't. But you would be safer to
leave your children with the average
undocumented immigrant compared to the
average citizen. They're 2.5 times less
likely to commit violent crimes compared
to the average US citizen.
>> I home school and that's why I'm a I'm a
mom. And my children come first. So, for
me, being able to do that is a blessing.
There's a lot of sacrifices that come
with that, especially in this economy. I
would be lying if I didn't say like it's
difficult with the gas prices. It's
difficult with the groceries and the
tariffs. There's a lot of things. Yeah,
similar with Biden there was a lot.
Inflation has not increased any uh same
amount as it did under Biden. So, the
money to Ukraine and the open border.
You can look and you can research about
how much it cost us to send the amount
of money that we did to Ukraine and what
it did to affect our economy and also
with the undocumented immigrants. They
are getting medical. They were getting
money for
the
Similar with Biden, there was a lot.
Inflation has not increased any uh same
amount as it did under Biden. So,
>> Biden do to cause it?
>> The money to Ukraine and the open
border.
You can look and you can research about
how much it cost us to send the amount
of money that we did to Ukraine and what
>> money did we send to Ukraine
>> what it did to affect our economy. And
also with the undocumented immigrants,
they are getting medical.
>> They were getting money for food and
free housing.
>> How much money did we send to Ukraine in
4 years under Biden?
>> You tell me.
>> $220 billion approximately.
>> Okay.
>> Now, here's a thing. If you're going to
blame Biden's 9% high level of inflation
on $220 billion spent over the course of
4 years, then why don't we see like 50%
levels of inflation considering the fact
that in the last last year and a half
Donald Trump has passed the big
beautiful bill, which according to most
estimates it will is clocked in the cost
us around 3.4 trillion dollars over the
course of 10 years. Or the simple fact
that he's spending a billion dollars a
day on a war in Iran. He's going to send
just as much money or spend just as much
money on this war in Iran as Biden did
in 4 years on Ukraine in less than a
year. And on top of that the cherry is
Donald Trump has continued to fund
Ukraine. Blaming a 9% high level of
inflation on $220 billion worth of
expenditures nuts, especially when we
consider that the Biden-Harris
administration spent half of what the
Trump administration spent in their
first term.
>> I get what you're saying and I think
both of us at the end of the day we want
what's best for America. I think we have
different plans or strategies to get
there. But the main thing I did want to
come up here and say, I don't think you
really answered it was if Trump was the
worst president in our lifetime, how did
he win twice, if not three times,
depending on who you talk to? Exactly.
So, if he was that terrible, either were
the and I mean you can say are we dumb
as a box of rocks? Like are we the
stupidest people? I've been told I'm
internalized racism and internalized
misogyny. I would love for you to be
honest.
>> I don't think that anybody in the
circles particularly intelligent.
>> Okay. And I understand that that's how
people see us.
>> Yeah, we're going to stop we're going to
stop there. You've been voted out. Thank
you. Return to your seat.
>> Well, thank you for your time.
>> Thank you for your time, Tia.
>> If you want to be the next debater, get
to the chair in three, two, one.
>> Hi.
>> My name is Leia.
>> Nice to meet you.
>> Nice to meet you, too.
Um just a little background, I am
currently active duty in the United
States Marine Corps. I'm not here on
>> Be careful, hot takes.
>> I'm not here on behalf of the Department
of War, by the way. I also grew up in
Jerusalem, Israel. And I think that
Trump has done a lot for me personally,
and I feel like that's what we should
all be here speaking about to an extent.
Um I've gotten paid more under him. I've
gotten bonuses under him. Um the
military has tightened up under him. And
from that perspective, I he's my
commander-in-chief, and I I'm grateful
for that.
>> Um yeah, out of everybody sitting in
this circle, you have the most reason to
not support Trump. Could I tell you why?
>> love to know why.
>> Cuz you're an oath. You took an oath to
defend the Constitution from enemies
overseas and domestic, correct?
>> Correct.
>> Can we agree that an enemy to the
Constitution, domestic or foreign, would
be a person who thinks that the
Constitution should be terminated, is
intentionally and belligerently
infringing upon it?
>> Can you go in depth with that, please?
>> Well, I mean, I think that is all the
context that would be required to
understand an enemy. If there's somebody
that is intentionally and belligerently
infringing on the Constitution, has
suggested that maybe we should terminate
it before, can we agree that person
would be an enemy to the Constitution?
>> That would be an enemy. I I do agree
with you, but I don't agree with you if
you're saying that's what Trump has
done.
>> December of 2022, Trump went on Truth
Social and said that because of the 2020
election, uh the termination of all
rules, regulations, and articles,
including those found within the
Constitution, uh would be allowed. And
in the last year and a half of his
presidency, he has directly infringed on
the 14th Amendment, threatened the
first, threatened the second, infringed
on the fourth, infringed on the 10th,
and threatened to infringe on the 23rd,
on top of Article 1 and 2. Donald Trump
is a domestic enemy to the Constitution.
>> I do not agree with that whatsoever.
Just just because just because you're
stating all these things, again, I'd
like a fact check, but he he hasn't he
he hasn't um actually put those in
place.
>> Executive Order number 14160 was put in
place. It attempted to take birthright
citizenship away from the children born
to undocumented immigrants on American
soil. But that is a long-standing ruling
from SCOTUS, regardless of its Plyler v.
Doe in 1989, saying that undocumented
immigrants are within the jurisdiction
of the US, or US v. Wong Kim Ark in the
late 19th century, arguing that the only
people who do not have a constitutional
claim to birthright citizen would be
members of militant invading forces,
foreign diplomats, and Native Americans,
which was later updated through federal
law. We know for a fact that the 14th
Amendment covers the protection of
birthright citizenship for the children
born to undocumented immigrants. Donald
Trump says, "Well, I'm going to change
that." And passes an illegal,
unconstitutional executive order stating
otherwise. That is a domestic threat to
our Constitution that you, as a member
of our DOJ, as an active duty service
member of the Marines, uh should
absolutely protest and stand in
uh in wide opposition against.
>> So, um that I would not agree is makes
him a domestic enemy. Um this is
militant. This is what what I signed an
oath for and what I raised my right hand
for. It's militant and um that has not
affected us in that in that military
aspect. I I don't think so. If you could
give me an example of how so,
um as far as like immigration and and
all these these people who have joined
the military to get papers for their
parents and stuff like that, it whether
they were born here or not, it it it's
been in effect and it's been very
helpful for them.
>> What were your thoughts on Donald Trump
calling for the execution of six sitting
Democrats in Congress who reminded you
to abide by your oath?
>> Six what?
>> Six sitting Democrats in Congress posted
a video saying, "If you're given an
illegal order, you don't got to follow
it." And you know you should know that's
what the UCMJ says.
>> absolutely.
>> Trump called for their execution because
of that. What do you think?
>> I I I don't I don't know much about
that.
>> Yeah, I'll I'll I'll I'll tell you. So,
>> Yeah, please do.
>> he went on Truth Social, he responded to
an article talking about the six
Democrats in Congress who posted a video
saying like, "Oh, you're remember your
oath, don't follow any unlawful orders
if Trump were to give you one." And he
calls them seditious traitors. Follows
it up by saying "Traitors punishable by
death." And then he reposts a follower's
comment that says "Hang them George
Washington would." Okay? So, he falsely
accuses them of a crime they didn't
commit. You and me could agree it's not
treasonous to tell a military not to
follow unlawful orders, UCMJ once again,
and then he says, "Well, because of this
crime that he's accusing them of that
they didn't commit, they need to be
hung." That's him directly calling for
the execution of six Democrats in
Congress. They were just simply
reminding you of the UCMJ. How could you
stand by such a maniac?
>> No, honestly, um we have multiple times
gone against if if it does not follow
along with the UCMJ throughout history
and in the military, and they've been
awarded for that. If if our military
leader, and for example, Donald Trump is
one of them, but if they go against what
the UCMJ does, we are allowed to go
against that.
>> Yeah. That's what all the Democrats
That's all the Democrats were saying,
and then he said, "They need to die
because they said that."
>> No.
>> Yes. He said
>> He's He's said what Who needed to die?
>> That these Democrats. He said that their
sedition is punishable by death. Okay?
This This sedition that they didn't
commit, and then he followed it up by
reposting a comment that said, "Hang
them." Explicitly, "Hang them." That was
him calling for their execution. There's
no ifs, ands, or buts about it. I feel
like you're maybe one of the more
reasonable people that I've spoken with
today. You should be able to see this so
clearly. And maybe this might even be an
historical moment here on Surrounded
where I'm able to change the mind of a
guest on the show. That'd be huge.
>> That would be huge if it was going to
happen, but it's not.
>> Oh, my goodness.
>> We have to pause there.
>> My final Surrounded claim is Donald
Trump doesn't give a about any of
you.
>> If you want to debate Dean's claim, get
to the chair in 3 2 1.
>> Hi.
>> Hi, Dean.
>> Okay. Well, I think that my my claim
here is clear. Donald Trump doesn't give
a about anybody in the circle. What
I mean by that is just Donald Trump
generally doesn't care about women. He's
a very misogynistic
>> Promises made, promises kept.
>> Opposite.
>> Number one, he's got more women on his
cabinet than most presidents did.
>> And he's fired what, four of them?
>> Doesn't matter.
>> I think it does. Every person he's fired
so far has been a woman.
>> you fire them. Do you Pam Bondi did
nothing.
>> Yeah, she was a terrible AG.
>> Exactly.
>> Yeah.
>> She did and he didn't like that, so he
fired her.
>> Yeah. I think that she was a terrible AG
for
preventing the release of the files. I
digress. I'm interrupting you. Sorry, go
>> Well, and he pardoned the J6ers like he
said he would.
>> Yeah.
>> And now he created a weaponization fund,
which I think is great. And he forego
all his money, which is $10 billion, and
he took 1.7 billion, 1776,
to give to the people that refuse to
take shots,
that were fired because they didn't want
to get the vax,
um that were targeted by the Biden DOJ,
uh grannies that were thrown in prison,
people that literally just stepped foot
on the Capitol grounds and were thrown
in prison for years.
>> Yeah.
>> No tax on tips, no tax on social
security,
>> Mhm.
>> and the lowest prescription prices that
we've ever had.
>> Uh okay.
>> Safe borders, no more child trafficking.
>> Okay, uh listen, let's start
let's start with that $1.8 billion fund.
>> Yeah.
>> Uh you said it was his personal money,
that's not true. It's funded by the
taxpayers.
>> It's owed to him.
>> Secondarily, uh it is an absolute
disaster
it's it's crazy that our president is
willing to give $1.8 billion to people
such as the J6 terrorists.
>> Well, they're not terrorists.
>> Well, I mean, I think they are. For
instance, there were 176
people who were who were criminally
convicted of deadly assaults on police
officers. Take for example, DJ
Rodriguez, who drove a stun gun into
Officer Fanone's neck while Officer
Fanone was on the ground getting beat
with metal rods
>> It's been proven First of all, Layla,
>> grab his gun and kill him. And then DJ
Rodriguez pled guilty to doing this in
court after Officer Fanone's testimony
and his body camera footage proved it.
>> familiar with Roseann Boylan? She was
beaten to death by an officer, Layla
Morris. Okay, nobody talks about that.
Ashley Babbitt was killed, shot in the
neck. She was an unarmed woman, a
military woman. There was no need for
that. We went there People went there
peacefully and patriotically.
>> Yeah.
>> And that's why they were screaming "Hang
Mike Pence", right?
>> Well, yeah, but nobody that I saw
>> Was that peaceful?
>> Um they there was a lot of infiltrators.
There was over 300 FBI agents in there.
>> Oh, really? Who's FBI?
>> Exactly, who's FBI? Right, everybody
says that.
>> president on J6?
>> Doesn't matter.
>> It does.
>> I read about that the other day when you
said
that.
>> I read that and read it. Who's FBI?
Did he pardon any of the
>> It was under Obama.
>> Obama was president on J6?
>> He wasn't Obama he wasn't president on
J6. President Trump was.
>> Oh, my god.
>> Obama's the one who's been trying to
persecute him. Obama, Biden
>> So Obama from day one with the Russian
dossier, yeah. So Obama infiltrated
Trump's FBI?
>> He's the one not just Obama, but all the
leftists, all the deep state.
Nancy Pelosi, Nancy Pelosi.
>> Then why listen, here's the real
question.
>> national guard?
>> Well, apparently Donald Trump had the
ability to call them there and this has
been proven by his second term.
According to Donald Trump's
>> Did you not hear Nancy Pelosi?
Did you not hear Nancy Pelosi?
But My fault.
>> I want to do a quick litmus test on one
of the claims that you made about all
the J6 antifa terrorists that were
infiltrating the crowd to cause havoc.
>> I actually know that there was over 300
people dressed up as
>> So do we agree that everybody who was
criminally convicted on J6 has since
been pardoned by Trump?
>> I believe so.
>> So Donald Trump pardoned antifa
terrorists?
>> Um
>> And now he's offering them 1.2 billion
dollars.
>> though. A lot of the antifa people
didn't get charged.
>> give me some evidence for that, ma'am?
>> Well, I don't did Ray
>> So you don't believe in you don't
believe in things, right? Without having
So what's happening?
>> I believe in facts.
>> Okay, so Donald Trump cares about the
American people.
>> Maybe we should get back to that.
Okay.
>> So we got to pause there. You've been
voted out.
>> Have a good one.
>> All right. If you want to be the next
debater, get to the chair in 3 2 1.
>> Howdy howdy.
>> Hi.
>> Hi. Welcome.
>> Thank you. Would you like to carry on
with why you think that?
>> Trump doesn't care about you, doesn't
care about anybody in the circle because
he generally doesn't care about women.
You said a lifetime of vapid misogyny,
like the fact that he's a sexual
predator, that he's a rapist, that he's
overturned policy that has led to 60
pregnant victims per day being denied
access to abortion in 10 of every 50
states, or an attack on our economy.
Everything is worse off today than it
was a year and a half ago under Giga
Chad Biden. Uh I don't think he cares
about you.
>> He almost took a bullet for this
country.
>> [applause]
>> And he faces He's faced so many
assassination attempts.
>> Yeah.
>> He faces threats. As you should know, I
mean, you you cried with Charlie Kirk.
>> I mean, listen. Specifically, this will
be 10 seconds or less so we could get
back to the topic. I cried because I uh
I thought that it was a mass shooting.
My friend was less than 30 ft away. He
FaceTimed me running away saying, "Dean,
I think that there's a mass shooting
going on." And regardless of the fact
that I didn't like Charlie Kirk, I'll be
honest, I think that he's despicable. He
endorsed child torture. Um I still saw
the video of somebody that I personally
knew, okay, uh get their jugular ripped
open by bullet. It was it was rough. Uh
and yeah, I shed a tear. That was that
was uh very It was very intense. Uh but
listen, the topic is
>> humanized you.
>> The topic is Donald Trump doesn't
generally care about women. He doesn't
give a about anybody in the circle.
You're arguing that well, maybe he does
care about women because he took a
bullet for you.
>> he put his life on the line if he didn't
care?
>> Well, I think the reason why he's
willing to apparently take a bullet to
the ear isn't because he cares about you
or else we'd see that demonstrated
through his actions, words, and policy,
which obviously hasn't occurred. But
rather, maybe you took a bullet uh
because it was either the bullet or the
jail cell for his 34 felonies, attempted
coup on J6. And he wants that power. He
wants that adoration. He wants that
glory. He wants that fame. He wants his
name to be in the history books. That's
why he's illegally placing his name on
the Kennedy Center or attempting to uh
commit the conquest of America, usurping
uh Iran to be the 51st state, Venezuela
to be the 52nd, and Canada to be the
53rd. That's what he wants to get out of
it. He doesn't want to help you or once
again, we'd see that represented through
his policy, which we don't.
>> I vehemently disagree with that.
>> Okay.
>> He cares for law enforcement. He cares
for firefighters, mothers trying to get
pregnant, and it's disheartening that
the way you describe Trump it's like
you're describing a leader in the Middle
East, someone that's an actual dictator,
an actual fascist.
>> Um
>> For someone that has traveled
>> Yeah, I mean, true.
>> and has seen how other countries
operate, this is the best country in the
world and we're so lucky to have Donald
Trump as a president and I'm
disheartened that you can't see that.
>> Okay. You said that he cares about law
enforcement. Then why did he pardon 178
people who attempted to assault or kill
cops on J6?
>> On January 6th?
>> Yeah, he pardoned. Like we went over
this earlier. DJ Rodriguez, okay, drove
a stun gun into Officer Fanone's neck,
gave him a heart attack, he had to be
raced off to the hospital. DJ Rodriguez
was then thrown in jail for 10 years.
Trump says he's a patriot, gives him a
full and complete presidential pardon,
and has now created a $1.8 billion slush
fund that's going to line DJ's pockets.
Dude, there's no way he cares about cops
if that's what he's willing to give to a
would-be cop killer.
>> Mhm.
Well, honestly, I don't know all the
details of that.
>> If everything that I just said was true,
would you concede that Donald Trump does
not care about law enforcement?
>> I would be curious why he I mean, I
don't know what information he has that
I don't, so I would have to place my
trust in the president of the United
States.
>> Did you place your trust in Biden?
>> there. You've been voted out. Please
return to your seat. If you would like
to be the next debater, get to the chair
in 3, 2, 1.
>> Welcome back, Liz.
>> Hi.
>> All right. Well, I mean, you know my
thoughts. I think that Trump is the
worst president of your life and I think
that he consistently demonstrates that
through his rhetoric and policy. What
are your thoughts?
>> I love Trump. And honestly, I love
everything that Trump is doing with
Israel. I'm Jewish. I'm very pro-Israel.
I know how you feel about Israel, but I
feel like you probably don't know the
facts. I also love what Trump is doing
with Iran because he does care about
women. He wants to free the women of
Iran from the Islamic regime. He wants
to free the women all around the world
and you see Tell me what you like about
Iran or Palestine and how they treat
women.
>> Well, I actually want to start off with
the claim you made about Iran.
Is Donald Trump negotiating with the
IRGC to achieve a denuclearization
agreement today?
>> There's no negotiating with terrorists.
>> Okay, well according to Trump that's not
true. He says that there are active
ongoing negotiations and they're
performing greatly.
>> Yeah, of course.
>> Okay, so he's the Okay, so the reason
why I ask you this question is because
the IRGC isn't going anywhere because
Donald Trump has already said that he's
achieved all of his military objectives
in this war. He's already quote unquote
coup'd the IRGC and committed regime
change by just getting more quote
unquote moderate voices to lead the IRGC
and now he's actively negotiating like a
30-to-50-year agreement with them so
they will never have the ability to
nuclearize again. What this means is
that Donald Trump actually wants the
IRGC to stay in charge of Iran or else
this denuclearization effort that has
costed us 13 lives, a billion dollars a
day, and higher gas prices and oil
prices everywhere would be for nothing.
And because the IRGC is not going then
he wouldn't be negotiating with them.
He wouldn't be trying to get a a deal
with them. You don't You don't advocate
to get a deal with a party that you
don't think should exist.
>> Here's the thing. Islam right now is
taking over all of these countries.
They've taken over most of Europe.
They're starting to take over in the
United States. He has to do this in a
very careful manner. There are billions
of Islamists who are trying to take over
every They will not stop until they have
infiltrated every country.
>> This is so disgusting.
This is
How it's literally what they say.
>> It's It's so gross.
>> until Islam is in every single
household. That is what they say and
that is why we need Israel and that is
why Trump is going to do everything he
can in his power to annihilate the IRGC,
which is what needs to happen.
>> Jesus Christ. Okay, so first and
foremost, if I could compulsively puke
on this table without getting you dirty,
I probably would because everything that
you just said was legitimately
disgusting. First and foremost, for you
to demonize to to to demonize and turn
all Muslim people alive
>> Not
it is not anti-Muslim.
You said that
you said that there were billions of
Islamist infiltrating every crook and
cranny of the world. So I think that
Listen, I think that we absolutely
Let me Let me respond to what you said.
I I think that
Yes, if you pray in public, then all of
the sudden you're extremist. Go tell
that to every Christian evangelical that
put their that put their hand on Trump's
shoulder in the Oval Office on camera.
Oh, it's it's different because it's
another religion. Exactly. When it's
about Jesus No, listen to what I'm
saying here. Listen to Listen to what
I'm saying here.
Listen to what I'm saying here. When
it's about Jesus
Oh, that's right. And that's why they're
going into the West Bank. That's why
they're going into Gaza. That's why
they're going into Lebanon. Listen to
what I'm saying here.
Listen to what I'm saying here.
And what's going on in the West Bank
today?
Oh, yeah.
And what's going on in the West Bank
today?
And what's going on in the West Bank?
Well, listen.
We're getting all over the
Well, let's Listen, well hey, what I
wouldn't want to happen is like rapid
war crimes.
25-mile radius. One moment. I don't
think that any country has an inherent
right to exist. I think that people have
a right to self-determination. A country
is a collective of people. Countries
into themselves are not moral entities.
I am explaining it to you. Let me speak.
I don't want you to interrupt me. I want
to answer your last question. You asked
me a good one. You said, "Dean, do you
think that Israel has a right to exist?"
I think that that question is
incomprehensible. And the reason why I
say that question is incomprehensible is
because a state is not a body in which
has rights. People are entities in which
have rights. A collective of people
collectively have a right to
self-determination. But the social
construct of a state and a government is
just a figure of our imagination through
the collective of civilization. Not an
entity in which has rights. But I want
to respond to
I want to be able to respond to
everything
So
So listen, Liz Liz, what you're doing is
you're attempting to overwhelm me with
questions. Which is a Gish gallop. I
want to ensure that I have proper time
to go over every statement that has left
your mouth. Particularly the first
statement that you made about the
billions of Islamists calling them
radical because they pray in public.
Christians pray in public all the time.
>> pray in public. I call them radical
because they literally say that they
will be they will not stop until Islam
is in every single household in every
country and they have completely taken
over and you can see them say that
everywhere.
>> I think that every mainstream religion,
okay, wishes that everybody on Earth
agreed with their religion. Yes, of
course they do. Let me explain you why.
Are you Are you a Christian?
>> I'm Jewish.
>> Okay. Here, listen. I'm going to ask you
a question to the Christians in the
circle. Do you guys think that the only
way to get to heaven is to have faith in
the gospel?
>> Absolutely. Just Christ.
>> Amen. And now, I want you to put your
flag down, okay, if you don't want
everybody to go to heaven. Everybody
still has their flag up. What that tells
me is that everybody with their flag up
think flags up thinks that the only way
to get to heaven is to be a Christian,
okay, and they want everybody to go to
heaven. What does this mean? They want
everybody to be a Christian. So, from
this this line of argumentation,
everybody with their flag up is a
radical extremist, no different than the
Islamists that want everybody alive to
believe that uh that Muhammad is a
prophet.
>> have a question for the circle. All of
the Christians in the circle, do you
believe that if someone does not
recognize Jesus Christ as their Lord and
Savior, that they should be killed?
>> No.
>> Based.
>> Islam does.
>> So,
>> [cheering]
>> Okay.
>> Good question.
>> Yeah, so that's a really argument to
rebuttal. Listen, I agree that when you
read the Quran and the Hadiths through a
particularly fundamentalist scope, you
could absolutely yield the conclusion
that we should like, oh, kill everybody
that's not a that's not a Muslim, 110%.
And I disagree with that fundamentalist
interpretation of the Quran and the
Hadiths. And I think the people who
don't are crazy. But, we could do the
same thing to the Christian Bible. When
we look at the Christian Bible and we
read it through a fundamentalist scope,
well, then all of a sudden, it is
totally okay to own slaves because of
Leviticus 25:44-46,
genocide is totally fine sometimes
because of 1 Samuel 15:3 uh and it's
sometimes it's okay to like impregnate
kids because the historical
representation of Mary's age under a
fundamentalist scope
under a fundamentalist scope is that
Mary was around 13. And the reason why
I'm giving you the fundamentalist
interpretation of the Christian Bible
isn't to on Christianity as a whole
but is rather to say that when you read
any religious text through that
fundamentalist perspective you could
always grave you could always yield
grave immoralities like slavery,
pedophilia, or killing people who
disagree with you. The thing is is that
a lot of Christians alongside a lot of
Muslims don't hold to that
fundamentalist interpretation of their
respective religious text that yield
those grave immoralities and rather
practice their religion in a quite
benevolent way.
>> The issue is you have people in Iran who
are literally suffering. People who had
to flee Iran 47 years ago who are still
suffering to this day. People all around
the world because the Islamic
extremists,
the ones who are also in charge of a lot
of these countries, will kill you. They
will behead you. They will do whatever
they can to harm you if you do not
believe with what they believe in if you
do not agree that the Prophet Muhammad
is the one and only and Islam is the
only religion. And that should be
allowed in the world. So that's the
thing. We are dealing with this today
with Islam and that's where the issue
lies.
>> Okay, we're going to stop there. We're
out of time. Thank you. And thanks for
the dialogue.
All right. I just want to give snaps to
everybody in the circle so far. Good
job, Dean. Snaps to you. Good job. Let's
take a breath. It's been a heated
episode. For the last portion of this
video, I ask that you look around the
circle and select somebody who you want
to come back to the center and debate
their claim with.
>> Oh god. See
there's there's so many options here. I
don't know. People might hit me at home
for this one.
I wanted to respond to what she had to
say.
>> Yeah, let's do it. Get up here.
>> Yes.
>> [applause]
>> Well, I'll give you credit. You're
you're brave to pick me. So
that's good.
>> Or dumb.
>> My surrounded claim is that Democrats
sold our country out.
>> Can I have an explanation of what you
mean when you say that?
>> Well, first off, their open-border
policies, you know, sanctuary cities
which are completely unconstitutional.
Thank God we have a Sheriff Chad Bianco
running for governor. Hopefully we'll
eliminate that. You know, they said
Russia, Russia, Russia, right? About
President Trump. Well, who sold your
uranium to Russia? And I love when Trump
was talking to all of these European
countries. He says, "You guys keep
screaming Russia, Russia, Russia. Why
aren't you buying oil from us? Why are
you buying it from Russia?" So, there's
so many good things that Trump has done
and the Democrats have completely like
I'm from Iran originally. The fact that
Obama gave boatloads of cash to that
evil regime makes me so angry. So, I
love that Trump annihilated General
Soleimani and a proxy guy in Iraq offed
him because he killed killed tens 10,000
people, including women and children.
>> Okay. Yeah, a lot.
>> Yeah, yeah, so I am I am so happy for
him getting rid of the nuclear
facilities along with Benjamin Netanyahu
with the intelligence that they brought
in and the weapons and they are only
allies and the liberals hate Israel.
>> Yeah.
>> This was like it could have been World
War
if we didn't get rid of this stuff. You
and I might not be here the next 5 10
years.
>> hate Trump then.
>> No, I should love him because he just
stopped World War he stopped the deep
state from destroying this world. And
that's what Marxists do. That's what
Marxists do. They They have no grip on
reality. They have no God and they don't
understand what's actually going on
because they're they're more concerned
about putting men in women's bathrooms
and their sports.
>> Oh my goodness. What's a communist? Can
you define that word?
>> Yeah, it's somebody that thinks that we
should not have our own private
property. So, the government gets to
choose, which is I don't want the the
government to be my mommy and daddy,
okay? It's supposed to be a
representative government, which is
called a constitutional republic. We are
not a freaking democracy.
>> Okay. Well, we're not a democracy.
>> Yes. Yeah, go go look at John Adams and
what he said about democracies.
>> So, first and foremost,
you weren't necessarily right about what
a communist is. Com- Communism is a
stateless, classless, money-less
society. Now, onto your second point
here about us not being
>> it work? Did it work? Have you watched
Doctor Zhivago?
>> So, you say that we're not a democracy,
we're a constitutional republic.
>> Correct.
>> So,
a constitutional republic would be a
type of representative democracy. And
what I mean when I say that is these two
phrases are used interchangeably.
Because under a republic, what? We have
duly elected leaders that then
represent, okay, the interests of the
constituents of the nation. Under a
representative democracy, we have duly
elected leaders that represent the
constituents of the nation.
>> democracy is minus a constitution and
the rule of law.
>> What?
>> So, it it's basically if you're saying
you're a democracy, the 51% could go and
kill off the 49%.
>> a direct democracy.
>> yeah, pure democracy.
>> said that he took a bullet for the
American democracy, he was wrong?
>> Uh well, he likes to use that word, I
think, to reach out to the Democrats. I
believe he's wrong because I don't
believe we're a I don't believe we're a
democracy. I don't like the word
democracy. I like I have a like a twitch
when when I hear the word because
>> just like you go crazy.
>> hypocrisy, bureaucracy. I mean, it's
just it's
>> Okay, now another claim that he made
there is that about the
>> It makes me you want to throw up. I want
to throw up when I hear the word
democracy.
>> Yeah, MAGA. So, listen.
>> Okay, it's you said MAGA like a swear
word. Why did you say that like a swear
word? Isn't that a good thing, make
America great again?
>> Well, what's not a good thing is saying
that you're making America great again
by taking healthcare away from 10
million low-income Americans like Trump
did. Taking food stamps away from 3
did.
>> the fraud. He got away with it. He got
away with
>> Can I speak?
>> You're lying right now. You're lying.
>> So, I'll go ahead and restart and I'll
give you my sources at the end.
>> Okay.
>> Composure is important, ma'am.
>> No, oh, you're going to talk down to me?
I'm your elder. You have respect for
your elders.
>> So, first and foremost, Biden is your
elder and you don't have any respect for
him.
>> Well, because
he's he's he's an evil man.
>> Don't allow me to speak.
You asked me, why do I use MAGA like a
swear word? Because Donald Trump has
used that phrase, Make America Great
Again, to represent actions like taking
healthcare away from 10 million
low-income Americans through the big
beautiful bill per the reports from the
Congressional Budget Office, which is
ran by Republicans. Liberal estimates
are a little bit higher like 17 million
people. Took food stamps away from 3
million low-income Americans through the
big beautiful bill as well. And
according to the Center on Budget and
Policy Priorities, you reduce the
purchasing power of the average American
making under under $51,000 per year. He
refused to abide by a court order to pay
out food stamp benefits for 12 million
starving children in America during the
last 12 days of the government shutdown.
Okay, he's abused his power and
privilege as the president to position
himself above the law. One of the last
things that you said when you're up
there on the last prompt was, "Oh, I
thought everybody was above the law."
Except for Trump. Okay, a couple weeks
ago we woke up in a new America with a
new system of justice where you and
Trump could commit the same crime, tax
fraud. You could be thrown in jail for
it and he can't even be investigated for
it because of his deal with the IRS. And
all of those things, when they are used
to represent the claim, Make America
Great Again, absolutely do make MAGA a
slur. It's embarrassing to be MAGA. I
mean, get a grip, you guys. Get a grip.
And I said a lot there. I'll let you to
respond. But I have so much else to say.
You know, like you were talking about
like how we need to prevent Iran from
getting nukes. We're at a worse place
with Iran today than we were 10 years
ago thanks to Donald Trump. Obama got us
an agreement to prevent them from
nuclearizing until 2030. Donald Trump
tore it up because it has Obama's
signature on it. And about the whole
respect your elders thing. So, you can't
expect me to respect you because you're
older than me. If you're going to turn
around and call Biden a good American
man with great domestic policy, one of
the best presidents in modern American
history, a crazy lunatic evil man with a
crackhead with a crackhead son, even
though he's 30 years your elder.
It's on record. He said, "I'm not going
to get you know, you're not going to get
the million-dollar loan unless you stop
this investigation to Burisma which his
son was a part of and had zero
experience."
>> That's extortion. Why isn't he in jail?
>> so he should be because
because the deep state have the judges.
They have so much they've infiltrated
this country.
>> Donald Trump just hired 400 new judges
that are loyalists to him. Why doesn't
he Why doesn't he use one of them to get
Biden thrown in jail?
>> unfortunately, he doesn't get to pick
which judge is used. And a lot of these
judges are just evil.
>> Why doesn't he even try? He hasn't
tried.
>> There's been so many lies coming from
your mouth. I'm like twitching over
there. Every lie that I hear you said
people died on January 6th
that that um
>> I said that they tried to kill cops.
>> No, they did not try to kill cops. It
was self-defense. They were being
attacked. Four patriots died that day
and you don't hear anything except for
the one that that got shot by the the
cop. Yeah.
>> How about this? Can I ask you a
question?
>> there's four of them that died and zero
cops died that day. One cop died the
next day at 9:30 p.m. from a stroke. So
that was a lie. And I feel bad for
people like you and your age because
you're being indoctrinated with all this
evil. You you have no appreciation for
life. You're willing to kill the most
innocent and vulnerable. But if you were
the baby in the womb, guess what? You
wouldn't want to
be aborted. You'd be like, "Mommy,
please keep me safe. Me, please."
>> I don't even know what to respond to.
There's just a bunch of a big mess. Hey,
listen. Let's go ahead and start off
with this. I want to ask you some
general questions about your political
beliefs because I believe that you hold
them without much information.
Name one domestic policy that the
Biden-Harris administration influenced
to get passed through Congress then
signed into law that you don't like.
Keep in mind once again, policy is a
bill passed through Congress and signed
into law.
>> I I don't know that I just know what he
was saying.
>> amendments are in the constitution?
>> The fact many amendments are there in
the constitution?
You don't know how many articles?
How many How about this? How many
continents are there?
How many continents are there? Ma'am,
how many continents are there?
There's seven.
>> Oh, oh seven continents, I thought
countries. Sorry, countries. I thought
you were talking about countries. This
isn't I'm not doing an information war.
I'm doing what I saw him do. He
glorified a man on women's day. He's
trying to destroy reality of men and
women. That is a bad thing and that's a
Marxist thing. So, you know, you're
asking me all of these questions because
you're trying to get me. Okay, yeah, I
might not have all of these little
things that you remember, but what I
know is is common sense. And Biden
Biden's administration is not common
sense. They sold us out just like Obama
giving money to our enemies instead of
helping our our allies like Israel. Who
was the only country to stand and take
down those nuclear facilities that could
have caused World War Let me finish.
World War
Except for Israel. Israel was the only
one.
Donald Trump asked other countries to
help because they were affecting them,
too. And they had their tail between
their legs and did nothing.
>> So, ma'am, the reason why I picked you
to come up to the microphone knowing
that it'd be a disaster is because I
think that you are a very accurate
representation of where the right is at
today in modern political discourse and
American politics. I think that you and
many others are clueless
people who don't know what they're
talking about, have done no previous
investigation or research into the
American political system, can't even
name a bill that Biden passed that you
disagree with, yet you think he's a
devil, and blame Obama for all of your
problems including the FBI, quote and
quote, going into the J6 riots 4 years
after his administration was over. And I
think that it is a very important for
you, me, everybody in the circle, and
everybody watching at home to start
caring about the world that we live in,
start caring about critical thought, and
doing investigative research into our
beliefs and why we believe them before
our world is gone to this of
baseless claims, propaganda, and just
putrid nonsense that is highlighted in
the mouths and brains of politicians,
the president, and cable news. It's
important for us to think critically,
and that's something that I don't think
you do.
>> I think it's just straight-up one word,
projection. Left always projects. That's
it. You're projecting all of your
>> [clears throat]
>> faults on me because I actually have
life experience, which you don't have,
and I have been a liberal, and I stepped
out of that when I saw what they were
doing with my child at school, who I
pulled out and I'm homeschooling.
>> I've been on the earth for less years
than you have, but I've done more with
the years that I have. Okay, we got to
stop there. Okay. Thank you. Let's give
them
>> that.
>> Let's give them a round of applause for
Trump.
>> [applause and cheering]
>> Let's give a round of applause to Dean.
Thank you, Dean.
You want to let us know what you thought
about this episode, leave a comment, but
actually,
don't do that. Just go for a walk, take
a breath. That was a pretty heated
discussion. Tune in Wednesday for a
follow-up discussion with some of the
people in this episode. Thank you for
watching. Maybe let us know who you want
to see in the center next time.
We'll see you next time.
>> [applause]
>> I hate it so much just seeing people
will be so lost in their delusion, these
people who believe in these things so
undoubtedly to with a such a high level
of confidence are are morons.
>> Well, Dean is the typical liberal man,
and he will insult you when he's losing
an argument. How many times did he
insult me we had to stop?
>> I think that MAGA women often get
mischaracterized as uneducated or that
they're oppressed, and honestly, a lot
of MAGA women have come from liberal
backgrounds. They've taken a lot of
thought into why they believe what they
believe.
>> We're all MAGA in our own unique ways,
and I feel like people try to kind of
put us in one sort of box. And I think
MAGA is about being a free thinker and
having some common sense.
>> I I hold on to this baseline assumption
that although maybe not all humans are
rational, all humans have the capacity
to be rational to the extent required to
unify the nation politically over such
obvious truths.